[
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:24, what shall he have delivered up to God?",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "10 15:24",
        "answer": "the kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 1 Corinthians 10 passed through the sea?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:1",
        "answer": "all (our fathers)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:1, where were our fathers?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:1",
        "answer": "under the cloud"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who were destroyed of the destroyer in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:10",
        "answer": "some of them (our fathers) who also murmured"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:11, what are come upon us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:11",
        "answer": "the ends of the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Now all these things happened unto them for ensamples: and they are written.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 10:11",
        "answer": "for our admonition, upon whom the ends of the world are come"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:11, why did all these things happen unto them?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:11",
        "answer": "for ensamples"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:12, why let him that thinketh he standeth take heed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:12",
        "answer": "lest he fall"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 10 which uses the word: Wherefore let him that thinketh he standeth take heed lest he fall.",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 10:12",
        "answer": "Wherefore let him that thinketh he standeth take heed lest he fall."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:12, let who take heed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:12",
        "answer": "him that thinketh he standeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 10:13.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 10:13",
        "answer": "There hath no temptation taken you but such as is common to man: but God is faithful, who will not suffer you to be tempted above that ye are able; but will with the temptation also make a way to escape, that ye may be able to bear it."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:13, what will God not suffer?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:13",
        "answer": "you to be tempted above that ye are able"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is common to man in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:13",
        "answer": "temptation (that has taken you)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:13, what will God make?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:13",
        "answer": "a way to escape"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where in 1 Corinthians 10 flee?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:14",
        "answer": "from idolatry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Wherefore, my dearly beloved, flee from idolatry.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 10:14",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 10:14"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:15, how do I speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:15",
        "answer": "as to wise men"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the cup of blessing in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:16",
        "answer": "the communion of the blood of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the bread which we break in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:16",
        "answer": "the communion of the body of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:17, of what are we all partakers?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:17",
        "answer": "of that one bread"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:18, who are partakers of the altar?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:18",
        "answer": "they which eat of the sacrifices"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:18, behold whom?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:18",
        "answer": "Israel (after the flesh)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:19, what two are said to be any thing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:19",
        "answer": "the idol or that which is offered in sacrifice to idols"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:2, in what two were they baptized?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:2",
        "answer": "in the cloud and in the sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:2, unto whom were they baptized?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:2",
        "answer": "unto Moses"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:20, what would I not?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:20",
        "answer": "that ye should have fellowship with devils"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:20, to whom do the Gentiles sacrifice?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:20",
        "answer": "to devils"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1 Corinthians 10 what two cups can ye not drink?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:21",
        "answer": "the cup of the Lord, and the cup of devils"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom do we provoke in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:22",
        "answer": "the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"All things are lawful for me, but all things are not.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 10:23",
        "answer": "expedient: all things are lawful for me, but all things edify not"
    },
    {
        "question": "What edify not in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:23",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:23, what are not expedient?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:23",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 10 which uses the word: wealth",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 10:24",
        "answer": "Let no man seek his own, but every man another's wealth."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:24, let who seek his own?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:24",
        "answer": "no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who seek another's wealth in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:24",
        "answer": "every man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:25, what eat?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:25",
        "answer": "Whatsoever is sold in the shambles"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:25, for what ask no question?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:25",
        "answer": "for conscience sake"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:26, what two are the Lord's?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:26",
        "answer": "the earth is the Lord's, and the fulness thereof"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 10:26.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 10:26",
        "answer": "For the earth is the Lord's, and the fulness thereof."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who bid you to a feast in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:27",
        "answer": "any of them that believe not"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:27, what eat?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:27",
        "answer": "whatsoever is set before you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:28, for what two eat not?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:28",
        "answer": "for his sake that showed it, and for conscience sake"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:28, how is this offered?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:28",
        "answer": "in sacrifice unto idols"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:29, what is judged?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:29",
        "answer": "my liberty"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:3, what did all eat?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:3",
        "answer": "the same spiritual meat"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:30, by what am I a partaker?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:30",
        "answer": "by grace"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:30, for what am I evil spoken of?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:30",
        "answer": "for that for which I give thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:31, what do to the glory of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:31",
        "answer": "all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:31, how do all?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:31",
        "answer": "to the glory of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Whether therefore ye eat, or drink, or whatsoever ye do, do all to the glory of God.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 10:31",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 10:31"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:32, what give none?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:32",
        "answer": "offence"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:32, to what three give none offence?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:32",
        "answer": "neither to the Jews, nor to the Gentiles, nor to the church of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What am I not seeking in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:33",
        "answer": "mine own profit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:33, why do I seek the profit of many?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:33",
        "answer": "that they may be saved"
    },
    {
        "question": "What followed our fathers in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:4",
        "answer": "that spiritual Rock"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was that Rock in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:4",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And did all drink the same spiritual drink: for they drank of that spiritual Rock that followed them: and that Rock was Christ.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 10:4",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 10:4"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:5, who was not well pleased with many of our fathers?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:5",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where were our fathers overthrown in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:5",
        "answer": "in the wilderness"
    },
    {
        "question": "After what should we not lust in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:6",
        "answer": "evil things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:6, what were these things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:6",
        "answer": "our examples"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:7, what were some of them?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:7",
        "answer": "idolaters"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who sat down to eat and drink in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:7",
        "answer": "The people"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many fell in one day in 1 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 10:8",
        "answer": "three and twenty thousand"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:8, what did some of them commit?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:8",
        "answer": "fornication"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:9, how were some of them destroyed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:9",
        "answer": "of serpents"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 10:9, whom did some of them tempt?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 10:9",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:1, what be ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:1",
        "answer": "followers of me (even as I also am of Christ)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Be ye followers of me.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 11:1",
        "answer": "even as I also am of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:1, of whom am I a follower?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:1",
        "answer": "of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:10, what ought the woman to have on her head?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:10",
        "answer": "power"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:10, why ought the woman to have power on her head?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:10",
        "answer": "(For this cause) because of the angels"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:12, what are of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:12",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:12, who is of the man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:12",
        "answer": "the woman"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:13, how judge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:13",
        "answer": "in yourselves (is it comely that a woman pray unto God uncovered?)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:14, what is a shame unto a man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:14",
        "answer": "to have long hair"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 11 which uses the word: nature",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 11:14",
        "answer": "Doth not even nature itself teach you, that, if a man have long hair, it is a shame unto him?"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does nature teach you in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:14",
        "answer": "that, if a man have long hair, it is a shame unto him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:15, what is a glory to the woman?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:15",
        "answer": "long hair"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a covering for the woman in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:15",
        "answer": "her hair"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:16, what do we have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:16",
        "answer": "no such custom"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:16, who may seem to be contentious?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:16",
        "answer": "any man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:17, for what are ye come together?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:17",
        "answer": "for the worse"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:17, in what do I not praise you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:17",
        "answer": "in this that I declare unto you"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do I partly believe in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:18",
        "answer": "(it) that there be divisions among you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:18, when do I hear there are divisions among you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:18",
        "answer": "when ye come together in the church"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:19, what must also be among you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:19",
        "answer": "heresies"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:19, who may be made manifest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:19",
        "answer": "they which are approved"
    },
    {
        "question": "How remember me in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:2",
        "answer": "in all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:2, how do you keep the ordinances?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:2",
        "answer": "as I delivered them to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:20, where are ye come together?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:20",
        "answer": "into one place"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:21, what does every one take before the other?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:21",
        "answer": "his own supper"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:22, what have ye to eat and drink in?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:22",
        "answer": "houses"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:22, what despise ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:22",
        "answer": "the church of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:23, when did the Lord Jesus take bread?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:23",
        "answer": "the same night in which he was betrayed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was betrayed in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:23",
        "answer": "the Lord Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:23, what have I received of the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:23",
        "answer": "that which also I delivered unto you (That the Lord Jesus the same night in which he was betrayed took bread)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For I have received of the Lord that which also I delivered unto you, That the Lord Jesus the same night in which he was betrayed took bread:",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 11:23",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 11:23"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is broken for you in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:24",
        "answer": "my (Jesus') body"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And when he had given thanks, he brake it, and said, Take.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 11:24",
        "answer": "eat: this is my body, which is broken for you: this do in remembrance of me"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did he brake the bread in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:24",
        "answer": "when he had given thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:24, how do this?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:24",
        "answer": "in remembrance of me"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:25, what is this cup?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:25",
        "answer": "the new testament in my blood"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 11 which uses the word: supped",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 11:25",
        "answer": "After the same manner also he took the cup, when he had supped, saying, This cup is the new testament in my blood: this do ye, as oft as ye drink it, in remembrance of me."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:25, when did he take the cup?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:25",
        "answer": "when he had supped"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:25, when do ye in remembrance of me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:25",
        "answer": "as oft as ye drink it"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:26, what do ye show?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:26",
        "answer": "the Lord's death"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:26, how do ye show the Lord's death till he come?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:26",
        "answer": "as often as ye eat this bread, and drink this cup"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 11:26.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 11:26",
        "answer": "For as often as ye eat this bread, and drink this cup, ye do show the Lord's death till he come."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:27, of what shall he be guilty?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:27",
        "answer": "of the body and blood of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who shall be guilty of the body and blood of the Lord in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:27",
        "answer": "whosoever shall eat this bread, and drink this cup of the Lord, unworthily"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:28, what let a man do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:28",
        "answer": "examine himself (and so let him eat of that bread, and drink of that cup)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:29, what is he not discerning?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:29",
        "answer": "the Lord's body"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who eateth and drinketh damnation to himself in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:29",
        "answer": "he that eateth and drinketh unworthily"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:3, what is God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:3",
        "answer": "the head of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 11:3.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 11:3",
        "answer": "But I would have you know, that the head of every man is Christ; and the head of the woman is the man; and the head of Christ is God."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:3, who is the head of the woman?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:3",
        "answer": "the man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why are many sickly among you in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:30",
        "answer": "For this cause (eating the Lord's supper unworthily)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For if we would judge ourselves, we should not be judged.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 11:31",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 11:31"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:31, when should we not be judged?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:31",
        "answer": "if we would judge ourselves"
    },
    {
        "question": "How should we not be condemned in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:32",
        "answer": "with the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:32, of whom are we chastened?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:32",
        "answer": "of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:32, when are we chastened?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:32",
        "answer": "when we are judged"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But when we are judged, we are chastened.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 11:32",
        "answer": "of the Lord, that we should not be condemned with the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:33, when tarry one for another?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:33",
        "answer": "when ye come together to eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:34, where let him eat?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:34",
        "answer": "at home"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:34, when will I set the rest in order?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:34",
        "answer": "when I come"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who dishonoureth his head in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:4",
        "answer": "Every man praying or prophesying, having his head covered"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:5, what is as if she were shaven?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:5",
        "answer": "a woman that prayeth or prophesieth with her head uncovered"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who dishonoureth her head in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:5",
        "answer": "every woman that prayeth or prophesieth with her head uncovered"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:6, what is a shame?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:6",
        "answer": "for a woman to be shorn or shaven"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:7, why ought a man not to cover his head?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:7",
        "answer": "forasmuch as he is the image and glory of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:7, what is the glory of the man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:7",
        "answer": "the woman"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 11:8, who is not of the woman?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 11:8",
        "answer": "the man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was created for the man in 1 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 11:9",
        "answer": "the woman"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:1, concerning what, would I not have you ignorant?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:1",
        "answer": "spiritual gifts"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:1, what would I not have you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:1",
        "answer": "ignorant"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:10, of what are there divers kinds?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:10",
        "answer": "of tongues"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:10, of what is there discerning?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:10",
        "answer": "of spirits"
    },
    {
        "question": "How is the Spirit dividing to every man in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:11",
        "answer": "severally as he will"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:11, what do all these work?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:11",
        "answer": "that one and the selfsame Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 12 which uses the word: dividing",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 12:11",
        "answer": "But all these worketh that one and the selfsame Spirit, dividing to every man severally as he will."
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For as the body is one, and hath many members, and all the members.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 12:12",
        "answer": "of that one body, being many, are one body: so also is Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:12, what hath many members?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:12",
        "answer": "the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:12, what are one body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:12",
        "answer": "all the members of that one body (being many)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:13, by what are we all baptized?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:13",
        "answer": "by one Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:13, what four may we be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:13",
        "answer": "whether we be Jews or Gentiles, whether we be bond or free"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 12 which uses the word: bond",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 12:13",
        "answer": "For by one Spirit are we all baptized into one body, whether we be Jews or Gentiles, whether we be bond or free; and have been all made to drink into one Spirit."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:13, how have we all been made to drink?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:13",
        "answer": "into one Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:14, what is not one member, but many?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:14",
        "answer": "the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shall the foot say in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:15",
        "answer": "Because I am not the hand, I am not of the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shall the ear say in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:16",
        "answer": "Because I am not the eye, I am not of the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:18, who hath set the members in the body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:18",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 12:18.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 12:18",
        "answer": "But now hath God set the members every one of them in the body, as it hath pleased him."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:18, how hath God set the members in the body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:18",
        "answer": "as it hath pleased him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:2, what were ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:2",
        "answer": "Gentiles"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unto what were ye carried away in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:2",
        "answer": "unto these dumb idols"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:20, what are they?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:20",
        "answer": "many members, yet but one body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:21, what can the eye not say unto the hand?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:21",
        "answer": "I have no need of thee"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:22, what are those members that seem to be more feeble?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:22",
        "answer": "necessary"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:22, what do those members seem to be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:22",
        "answer": "more feeble"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:23, upon what do we bestow more abundant honor?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:23",
        "answer": "those members of the body, which we think to be less honourable"
    },
    {
        "question": "What have more abundant comeliness in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:23",
        "answer": "our uncomely parts"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:24, to what has God given more abundant honour?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:24",
        "answer": "to that part which lacked"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:24, what have no need?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:24",
        "answer": "our comely parts"
    },
    {
        "question": "What hath God tempered together in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:24",
        "answer": "the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: That there should be no schism in the body; but that the members should have the same care one for another.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 12:25",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 12:25"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where should there be no schism in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:25",
        "answer": "in the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:25, what should have the same care one for another?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:25",
        "answer": "the members"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:26, when do all the members rejoice?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:26",
        "answer": "when one member be honoured"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:26, when do all members suffer?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:26",
        "answer": "whether one member suffer"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Now ye are the body of Christ.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 12:27",
        "answer": "and members in particular"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:27, what are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:27",
        "answer": "the body of Christ (and members in particular)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:28, where hath God set some?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:28",
        "answer": "in the church"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:28, when hath God set apostles in the church?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:28",
        "answer": "first"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who calleth Jesus accursed in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:3",
        "answer": "no man speaking by the Spirit of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:3, but by whom can no man say that Jesus is the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:3",
        "answer": "the Holy Ghost"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:31, what do I show unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:31",
        "answer": "a more excellent way"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 12:31.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 12:31",
        "answer": "But covet earnestly the best gifts: and yet show I unto you a more excellent way."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is more excellent in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:31",
        "answer": "the way I show unto you"
    },
    {
        "question": "What covet earnestly in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:31",
        "answer": "the best gifts"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 12:4.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 12:4",
        "answer": "Now there are diversities of gifts, but the same Spirit."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:4, of what are there diversities?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:4",
        "answer": "of gifts"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:5, who is the same?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:5",
        "answer": "the same Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of what are there differences in 1 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 12:5",
        "answer": "of administrations"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:6, who worketh all in all?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:6",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:6, of what are there diversities?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:6",
        "answer": "of operations"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:7, what is given to every man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:7",
        "answer": "the manifestation of the Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: But the manifestation of the Spirit is given to every man to profit withal.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 12:7",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 12:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:7, why is the manifestation of the Spirit is given to every man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:7",
        "answer": "to profit withal"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:8, what two words are given by the same Spirit?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:8",
        "answer": "the word of wisdom and the word of knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 12:9, what two are given by the same Spirit?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 12:9",
        "answer": "faith and the gifts of healing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Though I speak with the tongues of men and of angels, and have not charity, I am become as sounding brass, or a tinkling cymbal.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 13:1",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 13:1"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:1, when am I become as sounding brass, or a tinkling cymbal?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:1",
        "answer": "if I have not charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:1, with what two tongues might I speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:1",
        "answer": "with the tongues of men and of angels"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:1, as what am I become if I have not charity?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:1",
        "answer": "as sounding brass, or a tinkling cymbal"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:10, when shall that which is in part be done away?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:10",
        "answer": "when that which is perfect is come"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:11, what three things did I do when I was a child?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:11",
        "answer": "I spake as a child, I understood as a child, I thought as a child"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"When I was a child, I spake as a child, I understood as a child.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 13:11",
        "answer": "I thought as a child: but when I became a man, I put away childish things"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did I put away childish things in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:11",
        "answer": "when I became a man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:11, when did I think as a child?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:11",
        "answer": "When I was a child"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:11, what did I put away when I became a man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:11",
        "answer": "childish things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:12, how shall I then know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:12",
        "answer": "even as also I am known"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:12, how will I then see?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:12",
        "answer": "face to face"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:12, when do we see darkly?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:12",
        "answer": "now"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 13:12.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 13:12",
        "answer": "For now we see through a glass, darkly; but then face to face: now I know in part; but then shall I know even as also I am known."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:12, how do I now know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:12",
        "answer": "in part"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And now abideth faith, hope, charity.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 13:13",
        "answer": "these three; but the greatest of these is charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the greatest of these in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:13",
        "answer": "charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "What now abideth in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:13",
        "answer": "faith, hope, charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:13, what is charity?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:13",
        "answer": "the greatest of these"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two in 1 Corinthians 13 may I understand?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:2",
        "answer": "all mysteries and all knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:2, what am I, if I have not charity?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:2",
        "answer": "nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "What could I remove in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:2",
        "answer": "mountains"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:2, what gift may I have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:2",
        "answer": "the gift of prophecy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 13 which uses the word: mountains",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 13:2",
        "answer": "And though I have the gift of prophecy, and understand all mysteries, and all knowledge; and though I have all faith, so that I could remove mountains, and have not charity, I am nothing."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:3, what might I give to be burned?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:3",
        "answer": "my body"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two profit me nothing if I have not charity in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:3",
        "answer": "though I bestow all my goods to feed the poor, and though I give my body to be burned"
    },
    {
        "question": "How might I bestow all my goods in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:3",
        "answer": "to feed the poor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And though I bestow all my goods to feed the poor.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 13:3",
        "answer": "and though I give my body to be burned, and have not charity, it profiteth me nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does it profit me in 1 Corinthians 13 if I have not charity?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:3",
        "answer": "nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:4, what three things does charity not do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:4",
        "answer": "envieth not, vaunteth not itself, is not puffed up"
    },
    {
        "question": "What envieth not in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:4",
        "answer": "charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:4, how does charity suffer?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:4",
        "answer": "long"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 13:4.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 13:4",
        "answer": "Charity suffereth long, and is kind; charity envieth not; charity vaunteth not itself, is not puffed up,"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:5, how is charity provoked?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:5",
        "answer": "not easily"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does charity behave itself in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:5",
        "answer": "not unseemly"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:5, what does charity think?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:5",
        "answer": "no evil"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:6, in what does charity not rejoice?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:6",
        "answer": "in iniquity"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does charity rejoice in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:6",
        "answer": "in the truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:7, what four things does charity do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:7",
        "answer": "Bear all things, believe all things, hope all things, endure all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "What endureth all things in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:7",
        "answer": "charity (v. 4)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:7, what does charity believe?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:7",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shall cease in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:8",
        "answer": "(they) tongues"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 13 which uses the word: vanish",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 13:8",
        "answer": "Charity never faileth: but whether there be prophecies, they shall fail; whether there be tongues, they shall cease; whether there be knowledge, it shall vanish away."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:8, what shall vanish away?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:8",
        "answer": "(it) knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shall fail in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:8",
        "answer": "(they) prophecies"
    },
    {
        "question": "What never faileth in 1 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 13:8",
        "answer": "Charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For we know in part, and we prophesy in part.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 13:9",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 13:9"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:9, how do we prophesy?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:9",
        "answer": "in part"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 13:9, how do we know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 13:9",
        "answer": "in part"
    },
    {
        "question": "What follow after in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:1",
        "answer": "charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:10, what is without signification?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:10",
        "answer": "none of them (the kinds of voices)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:10, what are in the world?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:10",
        "answer": "many kinds of voices"
    },
    {
        "question": "When shall I be a barbarian in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:11",
        "answer": "if I know not the meaning of the voice (of him that speaketh)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of what are ye zealous in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:12",
        "answer": "of spiritual gifts"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:12, what seek?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:12",
        "answer": "that ye may excel to the edifying of the church"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:13, what let him that speaketh in an unknown tongue pray?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:13",
        "answer": "that he may interpret"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:14, what prayeth if I pray in an unknown tongue?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:14",
        "answer": "my spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is unfruitful in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:14",
        "answer": "my understanding (if I pray in an unknown tongue)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:15, with what will I pray?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:15",
        "answer": "with the spirit, and I will pray with the understanding also"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: What is it then? I will pray with the spirit, and I will pray with the understanding also: I will sing with the spirit, and I will sing with the understanding also.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 14:15",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 14:15"
    },
    {
        "question": "With what will I sing in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:15",
        "answer": "with the spirit, and I will sing with the understanding also"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:16, how shalt thou bless?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:16",
        "answer": "with the spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:16, what does he not understand?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:16",
        "answer": "what thou sayest"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:17, what givest thou well?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:17",
        "answer": "thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:18, when do I speak with tongues?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:18",
        "answer": "more than ye all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:18, whom do I thank?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:18",
        "answer": "my God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:19, by what might I teach others also?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:19",
        "answer": "by my voice"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Yet in the church I had rather speak five words with my understanding.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 14:19",
        "answer": "that by my voice I might teach others also, than ten thousand words in an unknown tongue"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:19, what had I rather speak than 10,000 words in an unknown tongue?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:19",
        "answer": "five words with my understanding"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:2, unto whom does he that speaketh in an unknown tongue speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:2",
        "answer": "unto God"
    },
    {
        "question": "In malice, be ye what in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:20",
        "answer": "children"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 14:20.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 14:20",
        "answer": "Brethren, be not children in understanding: howbeit in malice be ye children, but in understanding be men."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:20, in understanding, be what?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:20",
        "answer": "men"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:21, with whom will I speak unto this people?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:21",
        "answer": "With men of other tongues (and other lips)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:21, where is it written?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:21",
        "answer": "In the law"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:22, what are for a sign?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:22",
        "answer": "tongues"
    },
    {
        "question": "What serveth for them which believe in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:22",
        "answer": "prophesying"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:23, what be come together in one place?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:23",
        "answer": "the whole church"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is convinced of all in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:24",
        "answer": "one that believeth not (or one unlearned that comes in to prophesying)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:25, what are made manifest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:25",
        "answer": "the secrets of his heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom will he worship in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:25",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:26, how let all things be done?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:26",
        "answer": "unto edifying"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:26, what five things have you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:26",
        "answer": "a psalm, hath a doctrine, hath a tongue, hath a revelation, hath an interpretation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:27, what let one do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:27",
        "answer": "interpret"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:28, where let him keep silence?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:28",
        "answer": "in the church (if there be no interpreter)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:29, what let the other do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:29",
        "answer": "judge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:29, how let the prophets speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:29",
        "answer": "two or three"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:3, to what does he that prophesieth speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:3",
        "answer": "to edification, and exhortation, and comfort"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:30, what let the first hold?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:30",
        "answer": "his peace"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:31, what may all be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:31",
        "answer": "comforted"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:31, how may we all prophesy?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:31",
        "answer": "one by one"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are subject to the prophets in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:32",
        "answer": "the spirits of the prophets"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is not the author of confusion in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:33",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 14 which uses the word: author",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 14:33",
        "answer": "For God is not the author of confusion, but of peace, as in all churches of the saints."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:33, of what is God the author?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:33",
        "answer": "of peace"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:34, let who keep silence in the churches?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:34",
        "answer": "your women"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where let them ask their husbands in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:35",
        "answer": "at home"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:35, what is a shame for women?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:35",
        "answer": "to speak in the church"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:37, what are the things that I write unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:37",
        "answer": "the commandments of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:38, what let him be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:38",
        "answer": "ignorant"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 1 Corinthians 14 covet?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:39",
        "answer": "to prophesy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: He that speaketh in an unknown tongue edifieth himself; but he that prophesieth edifieth the church.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 14:4",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 14:4"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:4, who edifieth himself?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:4",
        "answer": "he that speaketh in an unknown tongue"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:4, who edifieth the church?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:4",
        "answer": "he that prophesieth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:40, how let all things be done?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:40",
        "answer": "decently and in order"
    },
    {
        "question": "What let be done decently and in order in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:40",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Let all things be done decently and in order.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 14:40",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 14:40"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is greater in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:5",
        "answer": "he that prophesieth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:5, who may receive edifying?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:5",
        "answer": "the church"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:6, by what four may I speak to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:6",
        "answer": "by revelation, or by knowledge, or by prophesying, or by doctrine"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what do they give a distinction in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:7",
        "answer": "sounds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 14 which uses the word: harp",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 14:7",
        "answer": "And even things without life giving sound, whether pipe or harp, except they give a distinction in the sounds, how shall it be known what is piped or harped?"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For if the trumpet give an uncertain sound.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 14:8",
        "answer": "who shall prepare himself to the battle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What may give an uncertain sound in 1 Corinthians 14?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 14:8",
        "answer": "the trumpet"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:9, what kind of words shall make known what is spoken?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:9",
        "answer": "words easy to be understood"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 14:9, how shall ye speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 14:9",
        "answer": "into the air"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 14:9.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 14:9",
        "answer": "So likewise ye, except ye utter by the tongue words easy to be understood, how shall it be known what is spoken? for ye shall speak into the air."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:1, what do I declare unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:1",
        "answer": "the gospel (which I preached unto you)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:1, wherein do ye stand?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:1",
        "answer": "in the gospel (which I preached unto you)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: But by the grace of God I am what I am: and his grace which was bestowed upon me was not in vain; but I laboured more abundantly than they all: yet not I, but the grace of God which was with me.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 15:10",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 15:10"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:10, by what am I what I am?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:10",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "How in 1 Corinthians 15 did I labour?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:10",
        "answer": "more abundantly than they all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:10, what was not in vain?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:10",
        "answer": "his grace which was bestowed upon me"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:12, how is Christ preached?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:12",
        "answer": "that he rose from the dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:13, who is not risen, if there be no resurrection of the dead?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:13",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:14, what two are vain if Christ be not risen?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:14",
        "answer": "our preaching and your faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:15, what are we found?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:15",
        "answer": "false witnesses (of God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:17, what is your faith?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:17",
        "answer": "vain"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:17, where are ye yet?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:17",
        "answer": "in your sins"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 15:17.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 15:17",
        "answer": "And if Christ be not raised, your faith is vain; ye are yet in your sins."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are perished in 1 Corinthians 15, if Christ be not raised?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:18",
        "answer": "they also which are fallen asleep in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "When are we the most miserable of all men in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:19",
        "answer": "If in this life only we have hope in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 15 which uses the word: miserable",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 15:19",
        "answer": "If in this life only we have hope in Christ, we are of all men most miserable."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:2, how keep what I have preached unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:2",
        "answer": "in memory"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:20, what is Christ become?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:20",
        "answer": "the firstfruits of them that slept"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:20, when is Christ risen from the dead?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:20",
        "answer": "now"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:21, what two came by man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:21",
        "answer": "death and the resurrection of the dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:21, by whom came the resurrection of the dead?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:21",
        "answer": "man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:22, where do all die?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:22",
        "answer": "in Adam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where shall all be made alive in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:22",
        "answer": "in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:23, when does every man come?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:23",
        "answer": "in his own order"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:23, what is Christ?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:23",
        "answer": "the firstfruits"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:24, what cometh?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:24",
        "answer": "the end"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:24, what three shall he have put down?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:24",
        "answer": "all rule and all authority and power"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:25, when must he reign?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:25",
        "answer": "till he hath put all enemies under his feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where will Christ put all enemies in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:25",
        "answer": "under his feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the last enemy in 1 Corinthians 15 that shall be destroyed?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:26",
        "answer": "death"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:27, where hath he put all things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:27",
        "answer": "under his feet"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is excepted in 1 Corinthians 15 when he saith all things are put under him?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:27",
        "answer": "he which did put all things under him (God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shall be subdued unto him in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:28",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:28, unto whom shall the Son also himself be subject?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:28",
        "answer": "him that put all things under him (God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:3, how did Christ die for our sins?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:3",
        "answer": "according to the scriptures"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:3, when did I deliver unto you that which I also received?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:3",
        "answer": "first (of all)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 15:3.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 15:3",
        "answer": "For I delivered unto you first of all that which I also received, how that Christ died for our sins according to the scriptures;"
    },
    {
        "question": "When do we stand in jeopardy in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:30",
        "answer": "every hour"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:31, what do I have in Christ Jesus our Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:31",
        "answer": "your rejoicing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:31, when do I die?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:31",
        "answer": "daily"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:32, when do we die?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:32",
        "answer": "to morrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where had Paul fought with beasts in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:32",
        "answer": "at Ephesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What corrupt good manners in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:33",
        "answer": "evil communications"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Be not deceived.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 15:33",
        "answer": "evil communications corrupt good manners"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:34, how do I speak this?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:34",
        "answer": "to your shame"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:34, what do some not have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:34",
        "answer": "the knowledge of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "How awake in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:34",
        "answer": "to righteousness (and sin not)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:36, what is not quickened, except it die?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:36",
        "answer": "that which thou sowest"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:36, except what, that which thou sowest is not quickened?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:36",
        "answer": "except it die"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:37, what sowest thou?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:37",
        "answer": "bare grain (it may chance of wheat, or of some other grain)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:38, who giveth it a body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:38",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:38, how does God give it a body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:38",
        "answer": "as it hath pleased him (and to every seed his own body)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:39, what are four kinds of flesh?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:39",
        "answer": "one kind of flesh of men, another flesh of beasts, another of fishes, and another of birds"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:39, what is not the same flesh?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:39",
        "answer": "All flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And that he was buried, and that he rose again.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 15:4",
        "answer": "the third day according to the scriptures"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was buried in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:4",
        "answer": "(he) Christ (v. 3)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:4, when did he rise again?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:4",
        "answer": "the third day"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:40, what are two kinds of bodies?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:40",
        "answer": "celestial bodies, and bodies terrestrial"
    },
    {
        "question": "What differeth from another in glory in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:41",
        "answer": "(one) star"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:41, what are three glories?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:41",
        "answer": "one glory of the sun, and another glory of the moon, and another glory of the stars"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:42, how is it sown?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:42",
        "answer": "in corruption"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:42, how is it raised?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:42",
        "answer": "in incorruption"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:43, in what two is it sown?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:43",
        "answer": "in dishonour and in weakness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:44, what is it raised?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:44",
        "answer": "a spiritual body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:44, what is it sown?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:44",
        "answer": "a natural body"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was made a quickening spirit in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:45",
        "answer": "the last Adam"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:45, what was the first Adam made?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:45",
        "answer": "a living soul"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:46, what was first?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:46",
        "answer": "that which is natural"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:47, who is the Lord from heaven?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:47",
        "answer": "the second man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:47, who is of the earth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:47",
        "answer": "The first man"
    },
    {
        "question": "What have we borne in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:49",
        "answer": "the image of the earthy"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:5, of whom was he seen?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:5",
        "answer": "of Cephas, then of the twelve"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:50, what cannot inherit the kingdom of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:50",
        "answer": "flesh and blood"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:51, what shall we all be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:51",
        "answer": "changed"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:51, what do I show you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:51",
        "answer": "a mystery"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:52, how shall the dead be raised?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:52",
        "answer": "incorruptible"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:52, what shall sound?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:52",
        "answer": "the trumpet"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:53, what must this corruptible do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:53",
        "answer": "put on incorruption"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:53, what must put on immortality?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:53",
        "answer": "this mortal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is swallowed up in victory in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:54",
        "answer": "Death"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: O death, where is thy sting? O grave, where is thy victory?",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 15:55",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 15:55"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:56, what is the strength of sin?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:56",
        "answer": "the law"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the sting of death in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:56",
        "answer": "sin"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:57, what be to God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:57",
        "answer": "thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 15:57.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 15:57",
        "answer": "But thanks be to God, which giveth us the victory through our Lord Jesus Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:57, what does God give us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:57",
        "answer": "the victory (through our Lord Jesus Christ)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:58, when abound in the work of the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:58",
        "answer": "always"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why be stedfast and unmoveable in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:58",
        "answer": "forasmuch as ye know that your labour is not in vain in the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 15 which uses the word: unmoveable",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 15:58",
        "answer": "Therefore, my beloved brethren, be ye stedfast, unmoveable, always abounding in the work of the Lord, forasmuch as ye know that your labour is not in vain in the Lord."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who remain unto this present in 1 Corinthians 15?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:6",
        "answer": "the greater part (of the above 500 brethren who saw the resurrected Christ)"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many brethren saw Christ at once in 1 Corinthians 15 after his resurrection?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 15:6",
        "answer": "above five hundred brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:7, of whom was he seen after that?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:7",
        "answer": "of James; then of all the apostles."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:8, when was he seen of Paul?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:8",
        "answer": "last of all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:9, what am I?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:9",
        "answer": "the least of the apostles"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 15:9, why am I not meet to be called an apostle?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 15:9",
        "answer": "because I persecuted the church of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:1, to whom have I given order?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:1",
        "answer": "to the churches of Galatia"
    },
    {
        "question": "For whom is the collection in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:1",
        "answer": "the saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:10, how see that Timotheus may be with you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:10",
        "answer": "without fear"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:10, who worketh the work of the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:10",
        "answer": "(he) Timotheus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Now if Timotheus come, see that he may be with you without fear: for he worketh the work of the Lord, as I also do.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 16:10",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 16:10"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom conduct forth in peace in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:11",
        "answer": "(him) Timotheus (v. 10)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 16:11.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 16:11",
        "answer": "Let no man therefore despise him: but conduct him forth in peace, that he may come unto me: for I look for him with the brethren."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:11, let who despise him?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:11",
        "answer": "no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:12, when will Apollos come?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:12",
        "answer": "when he shall have convenient time"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom did I greatly desire to come unto you with the brethren in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:12",
        "answer": "(him) Apollos"
    },
    {
        "question": "How quit you in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:13",
        "answer": "like men"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where stand fast in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:13",
        "answer": "in the faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 16 which uses the word: quit",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 16:13",
        "answer": "Watch ye, stand fast in the faith, quit you like men, be strong."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:13, be what?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:13",
        "answer": "strong"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:14, how let all your things be done?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:14",
        "answer": "with charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Let all your things be done with charity.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 16:14",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 16:14"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who have addicted themselves to the ministry of the saints in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:15",
        "answer": "the house of Stephanas"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:15, what is the firstfruits of Achaia?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:15",
        "answer": "(it) the house of Stephanas"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:16, where submit yourselves?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:16",
        "answer": "unto such (the house of Stephanas), and to every one that helpeth with us, and laboureth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:17, of what am I glad?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:17",
        "answer": "of the coming of Stephanas and Fortunatus and Achaicus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:17, what have they supplied?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:17",
        "answer": "that which was lacking on your part"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"I am glad of the coming of Stephanas and Fortunatus.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 16:17",
        "answer": "and Achaicus: for that which was lacking on your part they have supplied"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:18, what have they refreshed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:18",
        "answer": "my spirit and yours"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:19, what is in the house of Aquila and Priscilla?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:19",
        "answer": "the church"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 1 Corinthians 16 salute you?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:19",
        "answer": "The churches of Asia, Aquila and Priscilla, with the church that is in their house."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:2, when let every one of you lay by him in store?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:2",
        "answer": "Upon the first day of the week"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:2, why let every one of you lay by him in store?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:2",
        "answer": "that there be no gatherings when I come"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 16 which uses the word: prospered",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 16:2",
        "answer": "Upon the first day of the week let every one of you lay by him in store, as God hath prospered him, that there be no gatherings when I come."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:2, how let every one of you lay by him in store?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:2",
        "answer": "as God hath prospered him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:20, who greet you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:20",
        "answer": "All the brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:20, how greet ye one another?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:20",
        "answer": "with an holy kiss"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose salutation was with his own hand in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:21",
        "answer": "The salutation of me Paul"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 16 which uses the word: Maranatha",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 16:22",
        "answer": "If any man love not the Lord Jesus Christ, let him be Anathema Maranatha."
    },
    {
        "question": "Let who be Anathema Maranatha in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:22",
        "answer": "If any man love not the Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 16:23.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 16:23",
        "answer": "The grace of our Lord Jesus Christ be with you."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:23, what be with you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:23",
        "answer": "The grace of our Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:24, what be with you all?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:24",
        "answer": "My love"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:24, in whom, my love be with you all?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:24",
        "answer": "in Christ Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:3, when will I send them?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:3",
        "answer": "when I come"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:3, where will I send them?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:3",
        "answer": "unto Jerusalem"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom will I send to bring your liberality unto Jerusalem in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:3",
        "answer": "whomsoever ye shall approve (by your letters)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:4, if what, they shall go with me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:4",
        "answer": "if it be meet that I go also"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:5, when will I now come unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:5",
        "answer": "when I shall pass through Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:5, where do I pass?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:5",
        "answer": "through Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:6, where may ye bring me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:6",
        "answer": "on my journey (whithersoever I go)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:6, where will I winter?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:6",
        "answer": "with you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:7, how long do I trust to tarry with you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:7",
        "answer": "a while"
    },
    {
        "question": "When will I tarry at Ephesus in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:8",
        "answer": "until Pentecost"
    },
    {
        "question": "Until Pentecost, where will I tarry in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:8",
        "answer": "at Ephesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 16:9, what are many?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 16:9",
        "answer": "many adversaries"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is opened unto me in 1 Corinthians 16?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 16:9",
        "answer": "a great door and effectual"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For a great door and effectual is opened unto me.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 16:9",
        "answer": "and there are many adversaries"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Sosthenes in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:1",
        "answer": "our (Paul's) brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:1, through what is Paul called to be an apostle?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:1",
        "answer": "the will of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:10, how be joined together in the same mind and in the same judgment?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:10",
        "answer": "perfectly"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:10, by what do I beseech you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:10",
        "answer": "the name of our Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do they of the house of Chloe declare unto me in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:11",
        "answer": "that there are contentions among you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:11, what are among you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:11",
        "answer": "contentions"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of what four in 1 Corinthians 1 do people say they are?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:12",
        "answer": "of Paul; and of Apollos; and of Cephas; and of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Is who divided in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:13",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:13, were you baptized how?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:13",
        "answer": "in the name of Paul"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:14, whom did I baptize?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:14",
        "answer": "(none of you but) Crispus and Gaius"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:15, what should any say?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:15",
        "answer": "that I had baptized in mine own name"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose household did Paul baptize in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:16",
        "answer": "the household of Stephanas"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:16, what know I not?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:16",
        "answer": "whether I baptized any other"
    },
    {
        "question": "What should be made of none effect in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:17",
        "answer": "the cross of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:17, what did Christ send me to do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:17",
        "answer": "to preach the gospel (not with wisdom of words)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 1 which uses the word: baptize",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 1:17",
        "answer": "For Christ sent me not to baptize, but to preach the gospel: not with wisdom of words, lest the cross of Christ should be made of none effect."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:18, what is foolishness?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:18",
        "answer": "the preaching of the cross (is to them that perish foolishness)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For the preaching of the cross is to them that perish foolishness; but unto us which are saved it is the power of God.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 1:18",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 1:18"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:18, what is the power of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:18",
        "answer": "the preaching of the cross (is... unto us which are saved... the power of God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What will happen to the understanding of the prudent in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:19",
        "answer": "I (God) will bring to nothing the understanding of the prudent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:19, what will be destroyed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:19",
        "answer": "the wisdom of the wise"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:2, where is the church of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:2",
        "answer": "at Corinth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:2, upon what do they call?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:2",
        "answer": "the name of Jesus Christ our Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "What hath God made foolish in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:20",
        "answer": "the wisdom of this world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:21, what pleased God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:21",
        "answer": "(it) by the foolishness of preaching to save them that believe"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:21, who knew not God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:21",
        "answer": "the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 1:21.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 1:21",
        "answer": "For after that in the wisdom of God the world by wisdom knew not God, it pleased God by the foolishness of preaching to save them that believe."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:22, who seek after wisdom?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:22",
        "answer": "the Greeks"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do the Jews require in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:22",
        "answer": "a sign"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unto whom is Christ a stumblingblock in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:23",
        "answer": "unto the Jews"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:23, what is Christ crucified unto the Greeks?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:23",
        "answer": "foolishness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:24, unto whom is Christ the power of God and the wisdom of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:24",
        "answer": "unto them which are called, both Jews and Greeks"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:24, what two things is Christ unto them which are called?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:24",
        "answer": "the power of God, and the wisdom of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is stronger than men in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:25",
        "answer": "the weakness of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Because the foolishness of God is wiser.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 1:25",
        "answer": "than men; and the weakness of God is stronger than men"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is wiser than men in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:25",
        "answer": "the foolishness of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:26, of what three are not many called?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:26",
        "answer": "not many wise men after the flesh, not many mighty, not many noble"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:26, what see ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:26",
        "answer": "your calling"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:27, what hath God chosen to confound the things which are mighty?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:27",
        "answer": "weak things of the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hath chosen the foolish things of the world to confound the wise in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:27",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 1 which uses the word: confound",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 1:27",
        "answer": "But God hath chosen the foolish things of the world to confound the wise; and God hath chosen the weak things of the world to confound the things which are mighty;"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:28, what will God bring to nought?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:28",
        "answer": "things that are"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:28, what three things hath God chosen to bring to nought things that are?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:28",
        "answer": "base things of the world, and things which are despised, and things which are not"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And base things of the world, and things which are despised, hath God chosen, yea, and things which are not, to bring to nought things that are:",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 1:28",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 1:28"
    },
    {
        "question": "What should glory in God's presence in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:29",
        "answer": "no flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 1:29.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 1:29",
        "answer": "That no flesh should glory in his presence."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:29, where should no flesh glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:29",
        "answer": "in his (God's) presence"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:3, from whom be grace and peace?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:3",
        "answer": "from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:3, who is God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:3",
        "answer": "our Father"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is made sanctification and redemption and wisdom and righteousness unto us in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:30",
        "answer": "Christ Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:30, what is Christ Jesus made unto us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:30",
        "answer": "wisdom, and righteousness, and sanctification, and redemption"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"That, according as it is written, He that glorieth.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 1:31",
        "answer": "let him glory in the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:31, let who glory in the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:31",
        "answer": "(him) He that glorieth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:31, how let him glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:31",
        "answer": "in the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:4, what is given you by Jesus Christ?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:4",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:4, when do I thank my God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:4",
        "answer": "always"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:5, in what three are ye enriched by him?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:5",
        "answer": "in every thing, in all utterance, and in all knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was confirmed in you in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:6",
        "answer": "the testimony of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "For what are ye waiting in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:7",
        "answer": "for the coming of our Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:7, in what come behind?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:7",
        "answer": "in no gift"
    },
    {
        "question": "When may ye be blameless in 1 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 1:8",
        "answer": "in the day of our Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:8, unto what shall Christ confirm you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:8",
        "answer": "unto the end"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"God is faithful, by whom ye were called.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 1:9",
        "answer": "unto the fellowship of his Son Jesus Christ our Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:9, what is God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:9",
        "answer": "faithful"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 1:9, how were ye called?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 1:9",
        "answer": "unto the fellowship of his Son Jesus Christ our Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:1, not with what did I come to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:1",
        "answer": "not with excellency of speech or of wisdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 1 Corinthians 2 was I declaring unto you?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:1",
        "answer": "the testimony of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And I, brethren, when I came to you, came not with excellency of speech or of wisdom, declaring unto you the testimony of God.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 2:1",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 2:1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who searcheth all things in 1 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:10",
        "answer": "the Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:10, who hath revealed them unto us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:10",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:10, what does the Spirit search?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:10",
        "answer": "all things (yea, the deep things of God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 2:10.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 2:10",
        "answer": "But God hath revealed them unto us by his Spirit: for the Spirit searcheth all things, yea, the deep things of God."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:11, who knoweth the things of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:11",
        "answer": "(no man, but) the Spirit of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:11, what does no man know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:11",
        "answer": "the things of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:12, whom have we received?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:12",
        "answer": "the spirit which is of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:12, why have we received the spirit which is of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:12",
        "answer": "that we might know the things that are freely given to us of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:12, how are the things given to us of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:12",
        "answer": "freely"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:13, in what do we speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:13",
        "answer": "in the words which the Holy Ghost teacheth"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 1 Corinthians 2 are we comparing?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:13",
        "answer": "spiritual things (with spiritual)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:14, what are the things of the Spirit of God unto the natural man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:14",
        "answer": "foolishness"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who receiveth not the things of the Spirit of God in 1 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:14",
        "answer": "the natural man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:14, why can he not know them?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:14",
        "answer": "because they are spiritually discerned"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But the natural man receiveth not the things of the Spirit.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 2:14",
        "answer": "of God: for they are foolishness unto him: neither can he know them, because they are spiritually discerned"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does one discern the things of the Spirit of God in 1 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:14",
        "answer": "spiritually"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: But he that is spiritual judgeth all things, yet he himself is judged of no man.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 2:15",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 2:15"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:15, of whom is he that is spiritual judged?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:15",
        "answer": "of no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:15, who judgeth all things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:15",
        "answer": "he that is spiritual"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:16, what do we have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:16",
        "answer": "the mind of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 2:2.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 2:2",
        "answer": "For I determined not to know any thing among you, save Jesus Christ, and him crucified."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:2, what did I determine?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:2",
        "answer": "not to know any thing among you, save Jesus Christ, and him crucified"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:2, how did I determine to know Christ among you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:2",
        "answer": "crucified"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:3, in what three was I with you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:3",
        "answer": "in weakness, and in fear, and in much trembling"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:4, of what are enticing words?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:4",
        "answer": "man's wisdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 2 which uses the word: demonstration",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 2:4",
        "answer": "And my speech and my preaching was not with enticing words of man's wisdom, but in demonstration of the Spirit and of power:"
    },
    {
        "question": "In demonstration of what was my speech and my preaching in 1 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:4",
        "answer": "of the Spirit and of power"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was not with enticing words of man's wisdom in 1 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:4",
        "answer": "my speech and my preaching (Paul's)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"That your faith should not stand.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 2:5",
        "answer": "in the wisdom of men, but in the power of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:5, how should your faith stand?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:5",
        "answer": "in the power of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:5, not in what should your faith stand?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:5",
        "answer": "not in the wisdom of men"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:5, what should not stand in the wisdom of men?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:5",
        "answer": "your faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:6, who come to nought?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:6",
        "answer": "the princes of this world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:6, what do we speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:6",
        "answer": "wisdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:6, where do we speak wisdom?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:6",
        "answer": "among them that are perfect"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unto what did God ordain the hidden wisdom in 1 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:7",
        "answer": "unto our glory"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:7, what do we speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:7",
        "answer": "the wisdom of God (in a mystery, even the hidden wisdom)"
    },
    {
        "question": "When did God ordain the hidden wisdom in 1 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:7",
        "answer": "before the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:7, in what do we speak the wisdom of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:7",
        "answer": "in a mystery"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:8, what would they not have done, had they known it?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:8",
        "answer": "crucified the Lord of glory"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:8, who knew the wisdom of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:8",
        "answer": "none of the princes of this world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:8, whom did they crucify?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:8",
        "answer": "the Lord of glory"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Which none of the princes of this world knew: for had they known it, they would not have crucified the Lord of glory.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 2:8",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 2:8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 2 which uses the word: entered",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 2:9",
        "answer": "But as it is written, Eye hath not seen, nor ear heard, neither have entered into the heart of man, the things which God hath prepared for them that love him."
    },
    {
        "question": "What have not entered into the heart of man in 1 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 2:9",
        "answer": "the things which God hath prepared for them that love him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:9, what is written?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:9",
        "answer": "(it) Eye hath not seen, nor ear heard, neither have entered into the heart of man, the things which God hath prepared for them that love him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:9, where have the things which God hath prepared for them that love him not entered?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:9",
        "answer": "into the heart of man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:9, what hath not heard?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:9",
        "answer": "ear"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 2:9, what hath not seen?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 2:9",
        "answer": "Eye"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 3 which uses the word: babes",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 3:1",
        "answer": "And I, brethren, could not speak unto you as unto spiritual, but as unto carnal, even as unto babes in Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "How are ye babes in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:1",
        "answer": "in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:1, how could I not speak unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:1",
        "answer": "as unto spiritual"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:10, as what have I laid the foundation?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:10",
        "answer": "as a wise masterbuilder"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:10, what is given unto me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:10",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:10, how let every man take heed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:10",
        "answer": "how he buildeth thereupon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 3:11.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 3:11",
        "answer": "For other foundation can no man lay than that is laid, which is Jesus Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:11, what can no man lay?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:11",
        "answer": "other foundation (than that is laid)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:11, who is the foundation that is laid?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:11",
        "answer": "Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:12, upon what six may a man build?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:12",
        "answer": "gold, silver, precious stones, wood, hay, stubble"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:13, what shall be made manifest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:13",
        "answer": "Every man's work"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 3 which uses the word: try",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 3:13",
        "answer": "Every man's work shall be made manifest: for the day shall declare it, because it shall be revealed by fire; and the fire shall try every man's work of what sort it is."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:13, what shall declare it?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:13",
        "answer": "the day"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shall try every man's work in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:13",
        "answer": "the fire"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:14, what shall he receive?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:14",
        "answer": "a reward"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who shall suffer loss in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:15",
        "answer": "If any man's work shall be burned"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:15, how shall he be saved?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:15",
        "answer": "yet so as by fire"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:16, what are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:16",
        "answer": "the temple of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who dwelleth in you in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:16",
        "answer": "the Spirit of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Know ye not that ye are the temple of God, and that the Spirit of God dwelleth in you?",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 3:16",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 3:16"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:17, what is holy?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:17",
        "answer": "the temple of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What may any man defile in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:17",
        "answer": "the temple of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 3 which uses the word: defile",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 3:17",
        "answer": "If any man defile the temple of God, him shall God destroy; for the temple of God is holy, which temple ye are."
    },
    {
        "question": "Let whom deceive himself in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:18",
        "answer": "no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:18, what may any man seem to be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:18",
        "answer": "wise in this world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:18, why let him become a fool?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:18",
        "answer": "that he may be wise"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 1 Corinthians 3 is foolishness with God?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:19",
        "answer": "the wisdom of this world"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For the wisdom of this world is foolishness.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 3:19",
        "answer": "with God. For it is written, He taketh the wise in their own craftiness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:19, how does he take the wise?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:19",
        "answer": "in their own craftiness"
    },
    {
        "question": "How have I fed you in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:2",
        "answer": "with milk (and not with meat)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:2, when were you not able to bear it?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:2",
        "answer": "hitherto"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who knoweth the thoughts of the wise in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:20",
        "answer": "The Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the thoughts of the wise in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:20",
        "answer": "vain"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:21, how let no man glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:21",
        "answer": "in men"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:21, what are yours?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:21",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:23, who is God's?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:23",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:23, whose are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:23",
        "answer": "Christ's"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:3, what are ye yet?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:3",
        "answer": "carnal"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:3, how do ye walk?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:3",
        "answer": "as men"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 3:3.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 3:3",
        "answer": "For ye are yet carnal: for whereas there is among you envying, and strife, and divisions, are ye not carnal, and walk as men?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:4, of what two do they claim to be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:4",
        "answer": "of Paul or of Apollos"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:5, who gave to every man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:5",
        "answer": "the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:5, who are Paul and Apollos?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:5",
        "answer": "ministers by whom ye believed"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who gave the increase in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:6",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who watered in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:6",
        "answer": "Apollos"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"I have planted, Apollos watered.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 3:6",
        "answer": "but God gave the increase"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:6, what have I done?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:6",
        "answer": "planted"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: So then neither is he that planteth any thing, neither he that watereth; but God that giveth the increase.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 3:7",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 3:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:7, what does God do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:7",
        "answer": "giveth the increase"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:7, what two are not anything?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:7",
        "answer": "he that planteth, neither he that watereth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:8, how shall every man receive his own reward?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:8",
        "answer": "according to his own labour"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:8, what shall every man receive?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:8",
        "answer": "his own reward (according to his own labour)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 3:8, who are one?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 3:8",
        "answer": "he that planteth and he that watereth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose husbandry are ye in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:9",
        "answer": "God's"
    },
    {
        "question": "How are we labourers in 1 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 3:9",
        "answer": "together with God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:1, of what are we stewards?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:1",
        "answer": "of the mysteries of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "How account of us in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:1",
        "answer": "as of the ministers of Christ, and stewards of the mysteries of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: We are fools for Christ's sake, but ye are wise in Christ; we are weak, but ye are strong; ye are honourable, but we are despised.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 4:10",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 4:10"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:10, what three are we?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:10",
        "answer": "fools for Christ's sake, we are weak, we are despised"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:10, what three are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:10",
        "answer": "ye are wise in Christ; ye are strong; ye are honourable"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:11, what do we have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:11",
        "answer": "no certain dwellingplace"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:11, when do we hunger and thirst?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:11",
        "answer": "Even unto this present hour"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:12, how are we working?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:12",
        "answer": "with our own hands"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:12, what do we suffer?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:12",
        "answer": "(it) persecuted"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:13, as what are we made?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:13",
        "answer": "as the filth of the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "When are we the offscouring of all things in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:13",
        "answer": "unto this day"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do I warn you in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:14",
        "answer": "as my beloved sons"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:14, how do I not write these things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:14",
        "answer": "to shame you"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 4:14.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 4:14",
        "answer": "I write not these things to shame you, but as my beloved sons I warn you."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:15, in whom have I begotten you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:15",
        "answer": "in Christ Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1 Corinthians 4, how many fathers do you have?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:15",
        "answer": "not many"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many instructors do ye have in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:15",
        "answer": "ten thousand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 4 which uses the word: begotten",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 4:15",
        "answer": "For though ye have ten thousand instructors in Christ, yet have ye not many fathers: for in Christ Jesus I have begotten you through the gospel."
    },
    {
        "question": "Through what have I begotten you in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:15",
        "answer": "through the gospel"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:16, what be ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:16",
        "answer": "followers of me (Paul)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Wherefore I beseech you, be ye followers of me.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 4:16",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 4:16"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:17, whom have I sent unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:17",
        "answer": "Timotheus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For this cause have I sent unto you Timotheus, who is my beloved son, and faithful in the Lord.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 4:17",
        "answer": "who shall bring you into remembrance of my ways which be in Christ, as I teach every where in every church"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 1 Corinthians 4 is Timotheus?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:17",
        "answer": "my beloved son (and faithful in the Lord)"
    },
    {
        "question": "In whom are my ways in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:17",
        "answer": "in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:17, where do I teach everywhere?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:17",
        "answer": "in every church."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:18, what are some?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:18",
        "answer": "puffed up"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:18, how are some puffed up?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:18",
        "answer": "as though I would not come to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:19, when will I come to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:19",
        "answer": "shortly"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:19, what will I know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:19",
        "answer": "the power"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 4:2.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 4:2",
        "answer": "Moreover it is required in stewards, that a man be found faithful."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is required in stewards in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:2",
        "answer": "that a man be found faithful"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:2, in whom is it required that a man be found faithful?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:2",
        "answer": "in stewards"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 4:20.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 4:20",
        "answer": "For the kingdom of God is not in word, but in power."
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 1 Corinthians 4 is not in word, but in power?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:20",
        "answer": "the kingdom of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:21, in which spirit shall I come unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:21",
        "answer": "in the spirit of meekness"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a very small thing in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:3",
        "answer": "(it) that I should be judged of you, or of man's judgment"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:3, whom do I judge not?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:3",
        "answer": "mine own self"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:4, what do I know by myself?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:4",
        "answer": "nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:4, who is the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:4",
        "answer": "he that judgeth me"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Therefore judge nothing before the time, until the Lord come, who both will bring.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 4:5",
        "answer": "to light the hidden things of darkness, and will make manifest the counsels of the hearts: and then shall every man have praise of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:5, what shall every man have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:5",
        "answer": "praise of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:5, when judge nothing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:5",
        "answer": "before the time (until the Lord come)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:5, what will the Lord bring to light?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:5",
        "answer": "the hidden things of darkness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:6, for what have I transferred these things to myself and to Apollos?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:6",
        "answer": "for your sakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:6, what might you learn in us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:6",
        "answer": "not to think of men above that which is written (that no one of you be puffed up for one against another)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 4 which uses the word: differ",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 4:7",
        "answer": "For who maketh thee to differ from another? and what hast thou that thou didst not receive? now if thou didst receive it, why dost thou glory, as if thou hadst not received it?"
    },
    {
        "question": "When are ye full in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:8",
        "answer": "Now"
    },
    {
        "question": "How have ye reigned in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:8",
        "answer": "as kings (without us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:9, what are we made?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:9",
        "answer": "a spectacle"
    },
    {
        "question": "To what were we appointed in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:9",
        "answer": "to death"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 4:9, when hath God set forth us the apostles?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 4:9",
        "answer": "last"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are we made a spectacle in 1 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 4:9",
        "answer": "unto the world, and to angels, and to men"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is such fornication not as much as named in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:1",
        "answer": "among the Gentiles"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:1, what is the fornication that is among you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:1",
        "answer": "that one should have his father's wife"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: It is reported commonly that there is fornication among you, and such fornication as is not so much as named among the Gentiles, that one should have his father's wife.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 5:1",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 5:1"
    },
    {
        "question": "How is it reported that there is fornication among you in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:1",
        "answer": "commonly"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:1, what is among you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:1",
        "answer": "fornication (and such fornication as is not so much as named among the Gentiles, that one should have his father's wife)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where must ye needs go in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:10",
        "answer": "out of the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:10, not altogether with what four?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:10",
        "answer": "with the fornicators of this world, or with the covetous, or extortioners, or with idolaters"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:11, what have I written unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:11",
        "answer": "not to keep company, if any man that is called a brother be a fornicator, or covetous, or an idolater, or a railer, or a drunkard, or an extortioner; with such an one no not to eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "With what six in 1 Corinthians 5 are you not to eat?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:11",
        "answer": "fornicator, or covetous, or an idolater, or a railer, or a drunkard, or an extortioner"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 5 which uses the word: drunkard",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 5:11",
        "answer": "But now I have written unto you not to keep company, if any man that is called a brother be a fornicator, or covetous, or an idolater, or a railer, or a drunkard, or an extortioner; with such an one no not to eat."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:11, what two things have I written unto you not to do with such an one?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:11",
        "answer": "not to keep company, not to eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:12, whom do ye judge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:12",
        "answer": "them that are within"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 5:12.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 5:12",
        "answer": "For what have I to do to judge them also that are without? do not ye judge them that are within?"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do with that wicked person in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:13",
        "answer": "put (him) away from among yourselves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But them that are without God.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 5:13",
        "answer": "judgeth. Therefore put away from among yourselves that wicked person"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:13, who judgeth them that are without?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:13",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:13, whom does God judge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:13",
        "answer": "them that are without"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:13, whom put away from among yourselves?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:13",
        "answer": "that wicked person"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:2, what have ye not done?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:2",
        "answer": "mourned"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:2, who might be taken away from among you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:2",
        "answer": "he that hath done this deed"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:2, what are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:2",
        "answer": "puffed up"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:3, concerning whom have I judged?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:3",
        "answer": "him that hath so done this deed"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:3, when have I judged?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:3",
        "answer": "already"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:3, how am I present?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:3",
        "answer": "in spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:3, how am I absent?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:3",
        "answer": "in body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:4, with what power?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:4",
        "answer": "with the power of our Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:4, when?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:4",
        "answer": "when ye are gathered together"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:4, in whose name?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:4",
        "answer": "In the name of our Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:5, what may be saved?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:5",
        "answer": "the spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:5, when may the spirit be saved?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:5",
        "answer": "in the day of the Lord Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"To deliver such an one unto Satan for the destruction.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 5:5",
        "answer": "of the flesh, that the spirit may be saved in the day of the Lord Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why deliver such an one unto Satan in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:5",
        "answer": "for the destruction of the flesh (that the spirit may be saved in the day of the Lord Jesus)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where deliver such an one in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:5",
        "answer": "unto Satan"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:6, what does a little leaven leaveneth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:6",
        "answer": "the whole lump"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 5:6.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 5:6",
        "answer": "Your glorying is not good. Know ye not that a little leaven leaveneth the whole lump?"
    },
    {
        "question": "What leaveneth the whole lump in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:6",
        "answer": "a little leaven"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:6, what is not good?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:6",
        "answer": "Your glorying"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is sacrificed for us in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:7",
        "answer": "Christ our passover"
    },
    {
        "question": "What purge out in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:7",
        "answer": "the old leaven"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is our passover in 1 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 5:7",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:7, why purge out the old leaven?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:7",
        "answer": "that ye may be a new lump"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 5 which uses the word: passover",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 5:7",
        "answer": "Purge out therefore the old leaven, that ye may be a new lump, as ye are unleavened. For even Christ our passover is sacrificed for us:"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:8, what let us keep?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:8",
        "answer": "the feast"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Therefore let us keep the feast, not with old leaven, neither with the leaven of malice.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 5:8",
        "answer": "and wickedness; but with the unleavened bread of sincerity and truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:8, not with what three, let us keep the feast?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:8",
        "answer": "not with old leaven, neither with the leaven of malice and wickedness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:8, how let us keep the feast?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:8",
        "answer": "with the unleavened bread of sincerity and truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:9, with whom do not company?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:9",
        "answer": "with fornicators:"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:9, what did I write unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:9",
        "answer": "not to company with fornicators"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 5:9, in what did I write unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 5:9",
        "answer": "in an epistle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: I wrote unto you in an epistle not to company with fornicators:",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 5:9",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 5:9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Dare any of you, having a matter against another, go to law before the unjust, and not before the saints?",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 6:1",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 6:1"
    },
    {
        "question": "Before the unjust, to what do you go in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:1",
        "answer": "to law"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:1, when do you go to law before the unjust?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:1",
        "answer": "having a matter against another"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Nor thieves, nor covetous, nor drunkards, nor revilers.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 6:10",
        "answer": "nor extortioners, shall inherit the kingdom of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:11, in whose name are ye justified?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:11",
        "answer": "in the name of the Lord Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And such were some of you: but ye are washed, but ye are sanctified, but ye are justified in the name of the Lord Jesus, and by the Spirit of our God.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 6:11",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 6:11"
    },
    {
        "question": "How in 1 Corinthians 6 are ye justified?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:11",
        "answer": "in the name of the Lord Jesus, and by the Spirit of our God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:11, what three things are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:11",
        "answer": "washed, sanctified, justified (in the name of the Lord Jesus, and by the Spirit of our God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:12, what are lawful for me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:12",
        "answer": "All things"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 6:12.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 6:12",
        "answer": "All things are lawful unto me, but all things are not expedient: all things are lawful for me, but I will not be brought under the power of any."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:12, where will I not be brought?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:12",
        "answer": "under the power of any"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:13, for whom is the body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:13",
        "answer": "for the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 1 Corinthians 6 what two shall God destroy?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:13",
        "answer": "(it and them) the belly and meats"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:13, what is not for fornication?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:13",
        "answer": "the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:14, who hath raised up the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:14",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:14, how will God raise us up?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:14",
        "answer": "by his own power"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:15, who forbid?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:15",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are the members of Christ in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:15",
        "answer": "your bodies"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:16, what is one body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:16",
        "answer": "he which is joined to an harlot"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:16, what shall two be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:16",
        "answer": "one flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:17, who is one spirit?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:17",
        "answer": "he that is joined unto the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "How does he that committeth fornication sin in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:18",
        "answer": "against his own body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:18, what is without the body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:18",
        "answer": "Every sin that a man doeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "What flee in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:18",
        "answer": "fornication"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 6 which uses the word: Flee",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 6:18",
        "answer": "Flee fornication. Every sin that a man doeth is without the body; but he that committeth fornication sinneth against his own body."
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 6:19.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 6:19",
        "answer": "What? know ye not that your body is the temple of the Holy Ghost which is in you, which ye have of God, and ye are not your own?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:19, what is your body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:19",
        "answer": "the temple of the Holy Ghost"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:19, who is in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:19",
        "answer": "the Holy Ghost"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:2, who shall judge the world?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:2",
        "answer": "the saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "Are ye unworthy to judge what in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:2",
        "answer": "the smallest matters"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 6 which uses the word: unworthy",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 6:2",
        "answer": "Do ye not know that the saints shall judge the world? and if the world shall be judged by you, are ye unworthy to judge the smallest matters?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:20, how are ye bought?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:20",
        "answer": "with a price"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For ye are bought with a price: therefore glorify.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 6:20",
        "answer": "God in your body, and in your spirit, which are God's"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where glorify God in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:20",
        "answer": "in your body, and in your spirit (which are God's)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:3, whom shall we judge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:3",
        "answer": "angels"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:4, where are they least esteemed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:4",
        "answer": "in the church"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:4, of what do ye have judgments?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:4",
        "answer": "of things pertaining to this life"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where set them who are least esteemed in the church in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:4",
        "answer": "to judge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:5, to what do I speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:5",
        "answer": "to your shame"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:5, between whom shall one be able to judge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:5",
        "answer": "between his brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:6, before whom do they go to law?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:6",
        "answer": "before the unbelievers"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:6, who goes to law?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:6",
        "answer": "brother (goeth to law with brother)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:7, what do you not rather suffer?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:7",
        "answer": "yourselves to be defrauded"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is utterly among you in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:7",
        "answer": "a fault (because ye go to law one with another)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:8, what do ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:8",
        "answer": "wrong (and defraud)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom in 1 Corinthians 6 do ye defraud?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:8",
        "answer": "your brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shall the unrighteous not inherit in 1 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 6:9",
        "answer": "the kingdom of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 6:9.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 6:9",
        "answer": "Know ye not that the unrighteous shall not inherit the kingdom of God? Be not deceived: neither fornicators, nor idolaters, nor adulterers, nor effeminate, nor abusers of themselves with mankind,"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 6:9, be not what?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 6:9",
        "answer": "deceived"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:1, what is good for a man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:1",
        "answer": "not to touch a woman"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:10, what let not the wife do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:10",
        "answer": "depart from her husband"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:11, what let not the husband do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:11",
        "answer": "put away his wife"
    },
    {
        "question": "How let the wife remain, if she depart, in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:11",
        "answer": "unmarried"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:12, which wife let a brother not put away?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:12",
        "answer": "a wife that believeth not, and she be pleased to dwell with him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:13, whom leave not?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:13",
        "answer": "an husband that believeth not, and if he be pleased to dwell with her"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And the woman which hath an husband that believeth not, and if he be pleased to dwell with her, let her not leave him.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 7:13",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 7:13"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:14, who are holy?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:14",
        "answer": "your children"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:14, how is the unbelieving husband sanctified?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:14",
        "answer": "by the wife"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is not under bondage in 1 Corinthians 7 in such cases where the unbelieving spouse departs?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:15",
        "answer": "A brother or a sister"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:15, where hath God called us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:15",
        "answer": "to peace"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But as God hath distributed to every man, as the Lord.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 7:17",
        "answer": "hath called every one, so let him walk. And so ordain I in all churches"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:17, how let him walk?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:17",
        "answer": "as God hath distributed to every man OR as the Lord hath called every one"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do I so ordain in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:17",
        "answer": "in all churches"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:19, what two are nothing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:19",
        "answer": "Circumcision and uncircumcision"
    },
    {
        "question": "Avoid what in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:2",
        "answer": "fornication"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:2, what let every man have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:2",
        "answer": "his own wife"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 7:20.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 7:20",
        "answer": "Let every man abide in the same calling wherein he was called."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:20, where let every man abide?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:20",
        "answer": "in the same calling wherein he was called"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:21, what may thou be made?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:21",
        "answer": "free"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Lord's freeman in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:22",
        "answer": "he that is called in the Lord, being a servant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 7 which uses the word: freeman",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 7:22",
        "answer": "For he that is called in the Lord, being a servant, is the Lord's freeman: likewise also he that is called, being free, is Christ's servant."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:22, who is Christ's servant?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:22",
        "answer": "he that is called, being free"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:23, what be not ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:23",
        "answer": "the servants of men"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Ye are bought with a price; be not ye the servants of men.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 7:23",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 7:23"
    },
    {
        "question": "How are ye bought in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:23",
        "answer": "with a price"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:24, let who abide with God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:24",
        "answer": "every man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Brethren, let every man.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 7:24",
        "answer": "wherein he is called, therein abide with God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:25, concerning whom do I have no commandment?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:25",
        "answer": "virgins"
    },
    {
        "question": "What have I obtained in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:25",
        "answer": "mercy (of the Lord to be faithful)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:28, what shall such that marry have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:28",
        "answer": "trouble (in the flesh)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is short in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:29",
        "answer": "the time"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:29, how shall they that have wives be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:29",
        "answer": "as though they had none"
    },
    {
        "question": "What let the husband render unto the wife in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:3",
        "answer": "due benevolence"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 7 which uses the word: benevolence",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 7:3",
        "answer": "Let the husband render unto the wife due benevolence: and likewise also the wife unto the husband."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:30, how shall they that rejoice be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:30",
        "answer": "as though they rejoiced not"
    },
    {
        "question": "What passeth away in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:31",
        "answer": "the fashion of this world"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 7 which uses the word: belong",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 7:32",
        "answer": "But I would have you without carefulness. He that is unmarried careth for the things that belong to the Lord, how he may please the Lord:"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:32, who careth for the things that belong to the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:32",
        "answer": "He that is unmarried"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:33, who careth for the things that are of the world?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:33",
        "answer": "he that is married"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:34, who careth for the things of the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:34",
        "answer": "The unmarried woman"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is a difference in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:34",
        "answer": "between a wife and a virgin"
    },
    {
        "question": "How may ye attend upon the Lord in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:35",
        "answer": "without distraction"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:35, for what do I speak this?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:35",
        "answer": "for your own profit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:36, what let them do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:36",
        "answer": "marry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where hath he so decreed that he will keep his virgin in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:37",
        "answer": "in his heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:38, who doeth better?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:38",
        "answer": "he that giveth her not in marriage"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:38, who doeth well?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:38",
        "answer": "he that giveth her in marriage"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 7:39.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 7:39",
        "answer": "The wife is bound by the law as long as her husband liveth; but if her husband be dead, she is at liberty to be married to whom she will; only in the Lord."
    },
    {
        "question": "When is the wife bound by the law in 1 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 7:39",
        "answer": "as long as her husband liveth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:4, what does the wife not have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:4",
        "answer": "power of her own body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:40, what is she, if she so abide?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:40",
        "answer": "happier"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:5, to what may ye give yourselves?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:5",
        "answer": "to fasting and prayer"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:5, who may tempt you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:5",
        "answer": "Satan"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:6, how do I speak this?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:6",
        "answer": "by permission (and not of commandment)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:7, what does every man have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:7",
        "answer": "his proper gift of God (one after this manner, and another after that)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:8, what is good for the unmarried and widows?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:8",
        "answer": "if they abide even as I (remain unmarried)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 7:9, what is better than to burn?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 7:9",
        "answer": "to marry"
    },
    {
        "question": "What puffeth up in 1 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:1",
        "answer": "Knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:1, as touching what do we all have knowledge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:1",
        "answer": "things offered unto idols"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:1, what do we have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:1",
        "answer": "knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:1, what edifieth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:1",
        "answer": "charity"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Now as touching things offered unto idols, we know that we all have knowledge. Knowledge puffeth up, but charity edifieth.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 8:1",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 8:1"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:10, where may any man see thee sit?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:10",
        "answer": "at meat in the idol's temple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose conscience shall be emboldened to eat those things offered to idols in 1 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:10",
        "answer": "the conscience of him which is weak"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:10, what hast thou?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:10",
        "answer": "knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 1 Corinthians 8 died for the weak brother?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:11",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:11, through what shall the weaker brother perish?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:11",
        "answer": "thy knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:11, who shall perish?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:11",
        "answer": "the weak brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do you wound in 1 Corinthians 8 when you sin so against the brethren?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:12",
        "answer": "their weak conscience"
    },
    {
        "question": "When do you wound their weak conscience in 1 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:12",
        "answer": "when ye sin so against the brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:12, against which two do ye sin?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:12",
        "answer": "the brethren and Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:13, when will I eat no flesh?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:13",
        "answer": "while the world standeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 8 which uses the word: offend",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 8:13",
        "answer": "Wherefore, if meat make my brother to offend, I will eat no flesh while the world standeth, lest I make my brother to offend."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:13, why will I eat no flesh?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:13",
        "answer": "lest I make my brother to offend"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who may meat make to offend in 1 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:13",
        "answer": "my (weak) brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:2, what does he know as he ought to know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:2",
        "answer": "nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:2, who thinks that he knows anything?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:2",
        "answer": "any man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 8:2.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 8:2",
        "answer": "And if any man think that he knoweth any thing, he knoweth nothing yet as he ought to know."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:3, what is known of any man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:3",
        "answer": "(the same) if any man love God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:3, who does any man love?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:3",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But if any man love God.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 8:3",
        "answer": "the same is known of him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:4, where is an idol nothing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:4",
        "answer": "in the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: As concerning therefore the eating of those things that are offered in sacrifice unto idols, we know that an idol is nothing in the world, and that there is none other God but one.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 8:4",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 8:4"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:4, how are things offered unto idols?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:4",
        "answer": "in sacrifice"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:4, what is there none other but one?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:4",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:4, what two things do we know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:4",
        "answer": "that an idol is nothing in the world, and that there is none other God but one"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is nothing in the world in 1 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:4",
        "answer": "an idol"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:5, what two are many?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:5",
        "answer": "gods and lords"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:5, in what two places are there gods?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:5",
        "answer": "in heaven or in earth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:6, of whom are all things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:6",
        "answer": "(one) God, the Father"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:6, by whom are all things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:6",
        "answer": "(one) Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But to us there is but one God, the Father, of whom are all things.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 8:6",
        "answer": "and we in him; and one Lord Jesus Christ, by whom are all things, and we by him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:6, who is God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:6",
        "answer": "the Father"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:7, what is weak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:7",
        "answer": "their conscience"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 8 which uses the word: defiled",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 8:7",
        "answer": "Howbeit there is not in every man that knowledge: for some with conscience of the idol unto this hour eat it as a thing offered unto an idol; and their conscience being weak is defiled."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:7, what is not in every man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:7",
        "answer": "that knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:7, when do some eat?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:7",
        "answer": "unto this hour"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:7, with what do some eat?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:7",
        "answer": "with conscience of the idol"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is defiled in 1 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:7",
        "answer": "their conscience"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:7, as what do some eat?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:7",
        "answer": "as a thing offered unto an idol"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:8, when are we not better?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:8",
        "answer": "if we eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 1 Corinthians 8 commendeth us not to God?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:8",
        "answer": "meat"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 8:8.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 8:8",
        "answer": "But meat commendeth us not to God: for neither, if we eat, are we the better; neither, if we eat not, are we the worse."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:8, when are we not worse?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:8",
        "answer": "if we eat not"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why take heed in 1 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:9",
        "answer": "lest by any means this liberty of yours become a stumblingblock to them that are weak"
    },
    {
        "question": "What may become a stumblingblock in 1 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 8:9",
        "answer": "this liberty of yours"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: But take heed lest by any means this liberty of yours become a stumblingblock to them that are weak.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 8:9",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 8:9"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 8:9, to whom may your liberty become a stumblingblock?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 8:9",
        "answer": "to them that are weak"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:1, what are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:1",
        "answer": "my work in the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "How should he plow in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:10",
        "answer": "in hope"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:10, what should he that thresheth in hope be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:10",
        "answer": "partaker of his hope"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:11, what shall we reap?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:11",
        "answer": "your carnal things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:11, what have we sown unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:11",
        "answer": "spiritual things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:12, why have we suffered all things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:12",
        "answer": "lest we should hinder the gospel of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do they wait in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:13",
        "answer": "at the altar"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:13, who live of the things of the temple?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:13",
        "answer": "they which minister about holy things"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Even so hath the Lord ordained that they which preach.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 9:14",
        "answer": "the gospel should live of the gospel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What hath the Lord ordained in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:14",
        "answer": "that they which preach the gospel should live of the gospel"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:14, how should they which preach the gospel live?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:14",
        "answer": "of the gospel"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:15, what have I used?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:15",
        "answer": "none of these things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:15, what were better for me than that any man should make my glorying void?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:15",
        "answer": "(it) to die"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:16, what is laid upon me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:16",
        "answer": "necessity"
    },
    {
        "question": "When is woe unto me in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:16",
        "answer": "if I preach not the gospel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 9:16.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 9:16",
        "answer": "For though I preach the gospel, I have nothing to glory of: for necessity is laid upon me; yea, woe is unto me, if I preach not the gospel!"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:17, when do I have a reward?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:17",
        "answer": "if I do this thing willingly"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:17, what is committed unto me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:17",
        "answer": "a dispensation of the gospel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do I abuse not in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:18",
        "answer": "my power in the gospel"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:18, what may I make without charge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:18",
        "answer": "the gospel of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For though I be free from all men, yet have I made myself servant unto all, that I might gain the more.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 9:19",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 9:19"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:19, why have I made myself servant unto all?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:19",
        "answer": "that I might gain the more"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:19, from whom am I free?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:19",
        "answer": "all men"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:19, what have I made myself?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:19",
        "answer": "servant (unto all)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which seal are ye in the Lord in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:2",
        "answer": "the seal of mine (Paul's) apostleship"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:2, what am I to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:2",
        "answer": "an apostle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did I become as a Jew unto the Jews in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:20",
        "answer": "that I might gain the Jews"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 9 which uses the word: Jew",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 9:20",
        "answer": "And unto the Jews I became as a Jew, that I might gain the Jews; to them that are under the law, as under the law, that I might gain them that are under the law;"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:21, whom might I gain?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:21",
        "answer": "them that are without law"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"To the weak became I as weak, that I might gain.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "1C 9:22",
        "answer": "the weak: I am made all things to all men, that I might by all means save some"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:22, why am I made all things to all men?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:22",
        "answer": "that I might by all means save some"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:22, whom might I gain?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:22",
        "answer": "the weak"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:23, for what do I this?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:23",
        "answer": "for the gospel's sake"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:23, what might I be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:23",
        "answer": "partaker thereof (of the gospel with you)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:24, why so run?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:24",
        "answer": "that ye may obtain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 1 Corinthians 9:24.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "1C 9:24",
        "answer": "Know ye not that they which run in a race run all, but one receiveth the prize? So run, that ye may obtain."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:24, what does one receive?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:24",
        "answer": "the prize"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:25, what do they do it to obtain?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:25",
        "answer": "a corruptible crown"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is temperate in all things in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:25",
        "answer": "every man that striveth for the mastery"
    },
    {
        "question": "Not as what do I fight in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:26",
        "answer": "not as one that beateth the air"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:27, what do I bring into subjection?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:27",
        "answer": "my body"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 9 which uses the word: But I keep under my body, and bring it into subjection: lest that by any means, when I have preached to others, I myself should be a castaway.",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 9:27",
        "answer": "But I keep under my body, and bring it into subjection: lest that by any means, when I have preached to others, I myself should be a castaway."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:27, why do I bring my body into subjection?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:27",
        "answer": "lest that by any means, when I have preached to others, I myself should be a castaway"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:3, to whom is mine answer?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:3",
        "answer": "to them that do examine me"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:4, what have we power to do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:4",
        "answer": "to eat and to drink"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:5, as whom have we power to lead about a sister, a wife?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:5",
        "answer": "as other apostles, and as the brethren of the Lord, and Cephas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom have we power to lead about in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:5",
        "answer": "a sister, a wife"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:6, what two have power to forbear working?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:6",
        "answer": "(we, I only) Paul and Barnabas"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:6, what have we?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:6",
        "answer": "power to forbear working"
    },
    {
        "question": "What power do Barnabas and I have in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:6",
        "answer": "power to forbear working"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who eats of the fruit of the vineyard in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:7",
        "answer": "he who planteth a vineyard"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 1 Corinthians 9 which uses the word: vineyard",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "1C 9:7",
        "answer": "Who goeth a warfare any time at his own charges? who planteth a vineyard, and eateth not of the fruit thereof? or who feedeth a flock, and eateth not of the milk of the flock?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:7, who eats of the milk of the flock?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:7",
        "answer": "he who feedeth a flock"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:8, what saith the same also?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:8",
        "answer": "the law"
    },
    {
        "question": "What shalt thou not muzzle in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:9",
        "answer": "the mouth of the ox that treadeth out the corn"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 1 Corinthians 9:9, where is it written?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "1C 9:9",
        "answer": "in the law of Moses"
    },
    {
        "question": "What treadeth out the corn in 1 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "1C 9:9",
        "answer": "the ox"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For it is written in the law of Moses, Thou shalt not muzzle the mouth of the ox that treadeth out the corn. Doth God take care for oxen?",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "1C 9:9",
        "answer": "1 Corinthians 9:9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is base among you in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:1",
        "answer": "(I) Paul"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:1, when am I bold toward you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:1",
        "answer": "being absent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:1, by what do I beseech you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:1",
        "answer": "by the meekness and gentleness of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:10, what is his bodily presence?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:10",
        "answer": "weak"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are weighty in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:10",
        "answer": "his (Paul's) letters"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is contemptible in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:10",
        "answer": "his (Paul's) speech"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 10:10.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 10:10",
        "answer": "For his letters, say they, are weighty and powerful; but his bodily presence is weak, and his speech contemptible."
    },
    {
        "question": "What are powerful in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:10",
        "answer": "his (Paul's) letters"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:11, when are we in word by letters?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:11",
        "answer": "when we are absent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:11, when will we be also in deed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:11",
        "answer": "when we are present"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Let such an one think this, that, such as we are in word by letters when we are absent, such will we be also in deed when we are present.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 10:11",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 10:11"
    },
    {
        "question": "With whom do we dare not compare ourselves in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:12",
        "answer": "with some that commend themselves"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:12, who are not wise?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:12",
        "answer": "they measuring themselves by themselves, and comparing themselves among themselves"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:12, of what do we dare not make ourselves?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:12",
        "answer": "of the number"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 10 which uses the word: compare",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 10:12",
        "answer": "For we dare not make ourselves of the number, or compare ourselves with some that commend themselves: but they measuring themselves by themselves, and comparing themselves among themselves, are not wise."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does the measure reach in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:13",
        "answer": "even unto you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:13, of what will we not boast?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:13",
        "answer": "of things without our measure"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do we stretch not ourselves in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:14",
        "answer": "beyond our measure"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:14, what are we preaching?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:14",
        "answer": "the gospel of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:15, when shall we be enlarged?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:15",
        "answer": "when your faith is increased"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:15, of whose labours are we not boasting?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:15",
        "answer": "of other men's labours"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:15, what shall we be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:15",
        "answer": "enlarged (by you according to our rule abundantly)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:16, where to preach the gospel?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:16",
        "answer": "in the regions beyond you"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"To preach the gospel in the regions beyond you.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 10:16",
        "answer": "and not to boast in another man's line of things made ready to our hand"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:16, in what not to boast?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:16",
        "answer": "in another man's line of things (made ready to our hand)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:17, let whom glory in the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:17",
        "answer": "(him) he that glorieth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:17, how let him glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:17",
        "answer": "in the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 10:17.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 10:17",
        "answer": "But he that glorieth, let him glory in the Lord."
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For not he that commendeth himself is approved.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 10:18",
        "answer": "but whom the Lord commendeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:18, who is not approved?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:18",
        "answer": "he that commendeth himself"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:18, who is approved?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:18",
        "answer": "whom the Lord commendeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:2, when may I not be bold?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:2",
        "answer": "when I am present (with that confidence, wherewith I think to be bold against some)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:2, how do some think of us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:2",
        "answer": "as if we walked according to the flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 10 which uses the word: war",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 10:3",
        "answer": "For though we walk in the flesh, we do not war after the flesh:"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:3, how do we walk?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:3",
        "answer": "in the flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "After what do we not war in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:3",
        "answer": "after the flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Not what are the weapons of our warfare in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:4",
        "answer": "not carnal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is pulled down in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:4",
        "answer": "strong holds"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:4, what are mighty through God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:4",
        "answer": "the weapons of our warfare"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: (For the weapons of our warfare are not carnal, but mighty through God to the pulling down of strong holds;)",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 10:4",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 10:4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What exalteth itself against the knowledge of God in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:5",
        "answer": "every high thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:5, what two are we casting down?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:5",
        "answer": "imaginations, and every high thing that exalteth itself against the knowledge of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Casting down imaginations, and every high thing that exalteth itself against the knowledge.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 10:5",
        "answer": "of God, and bringing into captivity every thought to the obedience of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are we bringing into captivity in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:5",
        "answer": "every thought (to the obedience of Christ)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:5, to what are we bringing every thought into captivity?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:5",
        "answer": "to the obedience of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is fulfilled in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:6",
        "answer": "your obedience"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:6, what are we to revenge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:6",
        "answer": "all disobedience"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:7, whose are we?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:7",
        "answer": "Christ's"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:7, after what do ye look on things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:7",
        "answer": "after the outward appearance"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:8, of what should I boast somewhat more?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:8",
        "answer": "of our authority"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:8, what should I not be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:8",
        "answer": "ashamed"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 10:8, for what hath the Lord given us authority?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 10:8",
        "answer": "for edification"
    },
    {
        "question": "By what would I terrify you in 2 Corinthians 10?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 10:9",
        "answer": "by letters"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:1, where bear with me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:1",
        "answer": "in my folly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who shall stop me of this boasting in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:10",
        "answer": "no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:10, what is in me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:10",
        "answer": "the truth of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:11, who knoweth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:11",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What may I cut off in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:12",
        "answer": "occasion from them which desire occasion"
    },
    {
        "question": "Into what are they transforming themselves in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:13",
        "answer": "into the apostles of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:13, what kind of workers are transforming themselves into the apostles of Christ?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:13",
        "answer": "deceitful"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:14, how is Satan transformed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:14",
        "answer": "into an angel of light"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is transformed into an angel of light in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:14",
        "answer": "Satan (himself)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And no marvel; for Satan himself is transformed into an angel of light.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 11:14",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 11:14"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:15, what is no great thing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:15",
        "answer": "(it) if his (Satan's) ministers also be transformed as the ministers of righteousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 11:15.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 11:15",
        "answer": "Therefore it is no great thing if his ministers also be transformed as the ministers of righteousness; whose end shall be according to their works."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:15, what shall their end be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:15",
        "answer": "according to their works"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:16, how much may I boast myself?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:16",
        "answer": "a little"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:16, how receive me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:16",
        "answer": "as a fool (receive me)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:17, how do I speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:17",
        "answer": "(as it were) foolishly (in this confidence of boasting)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:18, how do many glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:18",
        "answer": "after the flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:19, what are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:19",
        "answer": "wise"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:19, how do ye suffer fools?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:19",
        "answer": "gladly"
    },
    {
        "question": "To whom have I espoused you in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:2",
        "answer": "to one husband"
    },
    {
        "question": "How am I jealous over you in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:2",
        "answer": "with godly jealousy"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:2, how may I present you to Christ?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:2",
        "answer": "as a chaste virgin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where may a man smite you in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:20",
        "answer": "on the face"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:20, what five do ye suffer?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:20",
        "answer": "if a man bring you into bondage, if a man devour you, if a man take of you, if a man exalt himself, if a man smite you on the face"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:21, as concerning what do I speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:21",
        "answer": "reproach"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 11 which uses the word: Abraham",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 11:22",
        "answer": "Are they Hebrews? so am I. Are they Israelites? so am I. Are they the seed of Abraham? so am I."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:22, what three are they?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:22",
        "answer": "Hebrews, Israelites, the seed of Abraham"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:22, Of whose seed are they?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:22",
        "answer": "the seed of Abraham"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was I in prisons in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:23",
        "answer": "more frequent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:23, in what was I above measure?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:23",
        "answer": "in stripes"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:24, of whom did I receive forty stripes save one?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:24",
        "answer": "Of the Jews"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times received I forty stripes save one in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:24",
        "answer": "five times"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Of the Jews five times received I forty stripes save one.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 11:24",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 11:24"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times was I beaten with rods in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:25",
        "answer": "Thrice"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:25, how many shipwrecks did I suffer?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:25",
        "answer": "thrice"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:25, when have I been in the deep?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:25",
        "answer": "a night and a day"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:26, In what eight perils was Paul?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:26",
        "answer": "in perils of waters, in perils of robbers, in perils by mine own countrymen, in perils by the heathen, in perils in the city, in perils in the wilderness, in perils in the sea, in perils among false brethren;"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:27, when was Paul in watchings?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:27",
        "answer": "often"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:28, what cometh upon me daily?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:28",
        "answer": "(that which) the care of all the churches"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Beside those things that are without, that which cometh upon me daily.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 11:28",
        "answer": "the care of all the churches"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who beguiled Eve in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:3",
        "answer": "the serpent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:3, what should be corrupted?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:3",
        "answer": "your minds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 11 which uses the word: Eve",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 11:3",
        "answer": "But I fear, lest by any means, as the serpent beguiled Eve through his subtlety, so your minds should be corrupted from the simplicity that is in Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "How did the serpent beguile Eve in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:3",
        "answer": "through his subtlety"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:30, of what will I glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:30",
        "answer": "of the things which concern mine infirmities"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 11 which uses the word: concern",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 11:30",
        "answer": "If I must needs glory, I will glory of the things which concern mine infirmities."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:31, what does the God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:31",
        "answer": "that I lie not"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:31, who is blessed for evermore?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:31",
        "answer": "The God and Father of our Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the governor desirous to do in Damascus in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:32",
        "answer": "to apprehend me (Paul)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who kept the city in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:32",
        "answer": "the governor (under Aretas the king)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the king in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:32",
        "answer": "Aretas"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did Paul escape in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:33",
        "answer": "his (the governor's) hands"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:33, how did Paul escape?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:33",
        "answer": "through a window in a basket was I let down by the wall"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 11:33.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 11:33",
        "answer": "And through a window in a basket was I let down by the wall, and escaped his hands."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:4, what does he preach?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:4",
        "answer": "another Jesus (whom we have not preached)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:4, what two might ye receive?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:4",
        "answer": "another spirit (which ye have not received) or another gospel (which ye have not accepted)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Paul not a whit behind in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:5",
        "answer": "the very chiefest apostles"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:6, how have we been made manifest among you in all things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:6",
        "answer": "thoroughly"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what am I rude in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:6",
        "answer": "in speech"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:7, what have I preached to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:7",
        "answer": "the gospel of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:7, how have I preached the gospel of God to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:7",
        "answer": "freely"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:8, why did I take wages of other churches?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:8",
        "answer": "to do you service"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom did I rob in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:8",
        "answer": "other churches"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And when I was present with you, and wanted, I was chargeable to no man: for that which was lacking to me the brethren.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 11:9",
        "answer": "which came from Macedonia supplied: and in all things I have kept myself from being burdensome unto you, and so will I keep myself"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 11:9, who supplied that which was lacking to me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 11:9",
        "answer": "the brethren which came from Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "To whom was I chargeable in 2 Corinthians 11?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 11:9",
        "answer": "to no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:1, to what will I come?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:1",
        "answer": "to visions and revelations of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:1, what is not expedient for me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:1",
        "answer": "(It) (doubtless) to glory"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 12 which uses the word: persecutions",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 12:10",
        "answer": "Therefore I take pleasure in infirmities, in reproaches, in necessities, in persecutions, in distresses for Christ's sake: for when I am weak, then am I strong."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:10, when am I strong?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:10",
        "answer": "when I am weak"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what five things in 2 Corinthians 12 do I take pleasure?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:10",
        "answer": "in infirmities, in reproaches, in necessities, in persecutions, in distresses"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what am I behind the very chiefest apostles in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:11",
        "answer": "in nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:11, how am I become a fool?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:11",
        "answer": "in glorying"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:12, in what were the signs of an apostle wrought among you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:12",
        "answer": "in all patience, in signs, and wonders, and mighty deeds"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Truly the signs of an apostle were wrought among you in all patience, in signs, and wonders, and mighty deeds.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 12:12",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 12:12"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were truly wrought among you in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:12",
        "answer": "the signs of an apostle"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:13, what was I not to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:13",
        "answer": "burdensome"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:13, what forgive me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:13",
        "answer": "this wrong"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:14, who ought not to lay up?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:14",
        "answer": "the children"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:14, which time am I ready to come to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:14",
        "answer": "the third time"
    },
    {
        "question": "What ought the parents to do in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:14",
        "answer": "to lay up for the children"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:15, how do I love you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:15",
        "answer": "the more abundantly"
    },
    {
        "question": "How will I spend in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:15",
        "answer": "very gladly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And I will very gladly spend and be spent for you.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 12:15",
        "answer": "though the more abundantly I love you, the less I be loved"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:16, with what did I catch you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:16",
        "answer": "with guile"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:17, did I make what of you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:17",
        "answer": "a gain"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:18, whom did I send with Titus?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:18",
        "answer": "a brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:18, in what two did we walk?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:18",
        "answer": "in the same spirit, in the same steps"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 12:19.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 12:19",
        "answer": "Again, think ye that we excuse ourselves unto you? we speak before God in Christ: but we do all things, dearly beloved, for your edifying."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:19, before whom do we speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:19",
        "answer": "before God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:19, what do we do for your edifying?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:19",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:19, how do we speak before God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:19",
        "answer": "in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:2, where was such an one caught up?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:2",
        "answer": "to the third heaven"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:2, when did I know a man in Christ?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:2",
        "answer": "above fourteen years ago"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:2, what can I not tell?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:2",
        "answer": "whether in the body or whether out of the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 12:2.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 12:2",
        "answer": "I knew a man in Christ above fourteen years ago, (whether in the body, I cannot tell; or whether out of the body, I cannot tell: God knoweth;) such an one caught up to the third heaven."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:20, what eight things do I fear there shall be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:20",
        "answer": "debates, envyings, wraths, strifes, backbitings, whisperings, swellings, tumults"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom shall I bewail in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:21",
        "answer": "many which have sinned already, and have not repented"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who will humble me among you in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:21",
        "answer": "my God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:21, of what three have many not repented?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:21",
        "answer": "of the uncleanness and fornication and lasciviousness (which they have committed)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:3, who knoweth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:3",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 12 which uses the word: paradise",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 12:4",
        "answer": "How that he was caught up into paradise, and heard unspeakable words, which it is not lawful for a man to utter."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:4, where was he caught up?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:4",
        "answer": "into paradise"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:4, what is not lawful?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:4",
        "answer": "(It) for a man to utter (unspeakable words)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 12 are unspeakable?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:4",
        "answer": "words (heard by the man caught up into paradise)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:5, in what will I glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:5",
        "answer": "in mine infirmities"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:6, what will I not be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:6",
        "answer": "a fool"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why did Paul forbear in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:6",
        "answer": "lest any man should think of me above that which he seeth me to be, or that he heareth of me"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:6, what will I say?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:6",
        "answer": "the truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the messenger of Satan in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:7",
        "answer": "a thorn in the flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And lest I should be exalted above measure through the abundance of the revelations, there was given to me a thorn in the flesh, the messenger of Satan to buffet me, lest I should be exalted above measure.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 12:7",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 12:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Why was a thorn in the flesh given to me in 2 Corinthians 12?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:7",
        "answer": "lest I should be exalted above measure"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:7, of what was there an abundance?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:7",
        "answer": "of the revelations"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For this thing I besought the Lord thrice.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 12:8",
        "answer": "that it might depart from me"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many times in 2 Corinthians 12 did Paul beseech the Lord for this thing?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 12:8",
        "answer": "thrice"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:8, how did I beseech the Lord for this thing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:8",
        "answer": "(thrice) that it might depart from me"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 12:9.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 12:9",
        "answer": "And he said unto me, My grace is sufficient for thee: for my strength is made perfect in weakness. Most gladly therefore will I rather glory in my infirmities, that the power of Christ may rest upon me."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:9, in what will I glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:9",
        "answer": "in my infirmities"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:9, why will I glory in my infirmities?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:9",
        "answer": "that the power of Christ may rest upon me"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:9, how is my strength made perfect?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:9",
        "answer": "in weakness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 12:9, what is sufficient?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 12:9",
        "answer": "My grace"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:1, what shall be established?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:1",
        "answer": "every word"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:1, which time is this that I am coming to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:1",
        "answer": "the third time"
    },
    {
        "question": "How shall every word be established in 2 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:1",
        "answer": "In the mouth of two or three witnesses"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:10, how do I write these things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:10",
        "answer": "being absent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:10, who hath given me power?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:10",
        "answer": "the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:10, to what hath the Lord given me power?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:10",
        "answer": "to edification"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:10, not to what hath the Lord given me power?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:10",
        "answer": "not to destruction"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 13 which uses the word: sharpness",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 13:10",
        "answer": "Therefore I write these things being absent, lest being present I should use sharpness, according to the power which the Lord hath given me to edification, and not to destruction."
    },
    {
        "question": "When should I use sharpness in 2 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:10",
        "answer": "being present"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:11, who shall be with you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:11",
        "answer": "the God of love and peace"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Finally, brethren, farewell. Be perfect, be of good comfort, be of one mind, live in peace; and the God of love and peace shall be with you.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 13:11",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 13:11"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:11, how live?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:11",
        "answer": "in peace"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:11, be what three things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:11",
        "answer": "Be perfect, be of good comfort, be of one mind"
    },
    {
        "question": "When farewell brethren in 2 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:11",
        "answer": "Finally"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 13:12.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 13:12",
        "answer": "Greet one another with an holy kiss."
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of kiss is used to greet one another in 2 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:12",
        "answer": "holy"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:12, how greet one another?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:12",
        "answer": "with an holy kiss."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 2 Corinthians 13 salute you?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:13",
        "answer": "All the saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:13, who salute you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:13",
        "answer": "All the saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of whom in 2 Corinthians 13 is the communion?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:14",
        "answer": "of the Holy Ghost"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"The grace of the Lord Jesus Christ.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 13:14",
        "answer": "and the love of God, and the communion of the Holy Ghost, be with you all. Amen"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:14, whose love be with you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:14",
        "answer": "the love of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:14, whose grace be with you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:14",
        "answer": "The grace of the Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:14, what be with you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:14",
        "answer": "The grace of the Lord Jesus Christ, and the love of God, and the communion of the Holy Ghost"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:2, to whom do I write?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:2",
        "answer": "to them which heretofore have sinned, and to all other"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:2, what will I not do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:2",
        "answer": "spare"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:2, which time?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:2",
        "answer": "the second time"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:2, being what, do I now write?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:2",
        "answer": "absent"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2 Corinthians 13 what proof do ye seek?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:3",
        "answer": "a proof of Christ speaking in me"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:3, what is mighty in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:3",
        "answer": "(a proof of) Christ speaking in me"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:4, how does he live?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:4",
        "answer": "by the power of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:4, by what shall we live?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:4",
        "answer": "by the power of God (toward you)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:4, through what was he crucified?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:4",
        "answer": "through weakness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:5, except what, Jesus Christ is in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:5",
        "answer": "except ye be reprobates"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 13:5.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 13:5",
        "answer": "Examine yourselves, whether ye be in the faith; prove your own selves. Know ye not your own selves, how that Jesus Christ is in you, except ye be reprobates?"
    },
    {
        "question": "How examine yourselves in 2 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:5",
        "answer": "whether ye be in the faith (prove your own selves)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:5, who is in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:5",
        "answer": "Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: But I trust that ye shall know that we are not reprobates.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 13:6",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 13:6"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:6, what shall ye know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:6",
        "answer": "that we are not reprobates"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:7, what should ye do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:7",
        "answer": "that which is honest"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:7, what do I pray to God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:7",
        "answer": "that ye do no evil"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:7, what should we appear?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:7",
        "answer": "approved"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Now I pray to God that ye do no evil; not that we should appear approved.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 13:7",
        "answer": "but that ye should do that which is honest, though we be as reprobates"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 13:8.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 13:8",
        "answer": "For we can do nothing against the truth, but for the truth."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:8, what can we do against the truth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:8",
        "answer": "nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:8, against what can we do nothing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:8",
        "answer": "the truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do we wish in 2 Corinthians 13?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 13:9",
        "answer": "(this) even your perfection"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 13:9, when are we glad?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 13:9",
        "answer": "when we are weak, and ye are strong"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 13 which uses the word: wish",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 13:9",
        "answer": "For we are glad, when we are weak, and ye are strong: and this also we wish, even your perfection."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:1, what is at Corinth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:1",
        "answer": "the church of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:1, what is Paul?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:1",
        "answer": "an apostle of Jesus Christ (by the will of God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Timothy in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:1",
        "answer": "our brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:1, who are in all Achaia?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:1",
        "answer": "(all the) saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:10, what do we trust that God will do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:10",
        "answer": "that he will yet deliver us"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:10, from what did God deliver us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:10",
        "answer": "so great a death"
    },
    {
        "question": "By what were ye helping together in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:11",
        "answer": "by prayer (for us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:11, what may be given by many on our behalf?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:11",
        "answer": "thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:12, by what have we had our conversation in the world, and more abundantly to you-ward?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:12",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where have we had our conversation in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:12",
        "answer": "in the world and (more abundantly) to you-ward"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:13, when do I trust ye shall acknowledge the things I write unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:13",
        "answer": "(even) to the end"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:13, what write we unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:13",
        "answer": "none other things, than what ye read or acknowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:14, what are we?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:14",
        "answer": "your rejoicing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:14, when are ye our rejoicing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:14",
        "answer": "in the day of the Lord Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:15, in what was I minded to come unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:15",
        "answer": "in this confidence"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:15, why was I minded to come unto you before?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:15",
        "answer": "that ye might have a second benefit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:16, where would I be brought on my way?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:16",
        "answer": "toward Judaea"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:16, out of where would I come again unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:16",
        "answer": "out of Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 2 Corinthians 1 is true?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:18",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:18, what was not yea and nay?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:18",
        "answer": "our word toward you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:19, who is Jesus Christ?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:19",
        "answer": "the Son of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What three preached Jesus Christ among you in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:19",
        "answer": "(me) Paul and Silvanus and Timotheus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:2, from whom is grace and peace?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:2",
        "answer": "from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:2, what be to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:2",
        "answer": "Grace and peace"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Grace be to you and peace from God our Father, and from the Lord Jesus Christ.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 1:2",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 1:2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are all the promises of God in him in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:20",
        "answer": "yea and Amen, (unto the glory of God by us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:20, unto what are all the promises of God yea and Amen in him?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:20",
        "answer": "unto the glory of God (by us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Now he which stablisheth us with you in Christ.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 1:21",
        "answer": "and hath anointed us, is God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where has God stablished us with you in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:21",
        "answer": "in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hath anointed us in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:21",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:22, what hath God given us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:22",
        "answer": "the earnest of the Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 1 which uses the word: sealed",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 1:22",
        "answer": "Who hath also sealed us, and given the earnest of the Spirit in our hearts."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:22, where hath God given the earnest of the Spirit?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:22",
        "answer": "in our hearts"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hath sealed us in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:22",
        "answer": "God (v. 21)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom do I call for a record in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:23",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:23, unto where did I come not as yet?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:23",
        "answer": "unto Corinth"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 1:23.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 1:23",
        "answer": "Moreover I call God for a record upon my soul, that to spare you I came not as yet unto Corinth."
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Not for that we have dominion over your faith, but are helpers of your joy: for by faith ye stand.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 1:24",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 1:24"
    },
    {
        "question": "Of what are we helpers in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:24",
        "answer": "of your joy"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:24, how do ye stand?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:24",
        "answer": "by faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:3, what are three titles of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:3",
        "answer": "the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies, and the God of all comfort"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Blessed be God, even the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 1:3",
        "answer": "the Father of mercies, and the God of all comfort"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 2 Corinthians 1 be blessed?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:3",
        "answer": "God (even the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies, and the God of all comfort)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 1:4.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 1:4",
        "answer": "Who comforteth us in all our tribulation, that we may be able to comfort them which are in any trouble, by the comfort wherewith we ourselves are comforted of God."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:4, by what may we be able to comfort them that are in any trouble?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:4",
        "answer": "the comfort wherewith we ourselves are comforted of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:4, whom may we be able to comfort?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:4",
        "answer": "them which are in any trouble"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:4, in what does God comfort us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:4",
        "answer": "in all our tribulation"
    },
    {
        "question": "What aboundeth by Christ in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:5",
        "answer": "our consolation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 1 which uses the word: aboundeth",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 1:5",
        "answer": "For as the sufferings of Christ abound in us, so our consolation also aboundeth by Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:5, what abound in us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:5",
        "answer": "the sufferings of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 1 are endured?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:6",
        "answer": "the same sufferings which we also suffer"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two are for your consolation and salvation in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:6",
        "answer": "(it) whether we be afflicted or whether we be comforted"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is stedfast in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:7",
        "answer": "our hope of you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:7, of what shall ye be partakers?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:7",
        "answer": "the consolation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And our hope of you is stedfast, knowing, that as ye are partakers of the sufferings, so shall ye be also of the consolation.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 1:7",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 1:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "How did we despair in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:8",
        "answer": "even of life"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where were we pressed out of measure in 2 Corinthians 1?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 1:8",
        "answer": "in Asia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:9, what does God do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:9",
        "answer": "raise the dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 1:9, what did we have in ourselves?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 1:9",
        "answer": "the sentence of death"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 2 did I determine with myself?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:1",
        "answer": "(this) that I would not come again to you in heaviness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:1, how would I not come again to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:1",
        "answer": "in heaviness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:10, whom do I forgive?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:10",
        "answer": "(To) whom ye forgive any thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:10, for what did I forgive any thing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:10",
        "answer": "for your sakes"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:10, in whose person did I forgive it?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:10",
        "answer": "the person of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:11, of what are we not ignorant?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:11",
        "answer": "of his (Satan's) devices"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Lest Satan should get an advantage of us: for we are not ignorant of his devices.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 2:11",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 2:11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What should Satan get in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:11",
        "answer": "an advantage of us"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who should get an advantage of us in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:11",
        "answer": "Satan"
    },
    {
        "question": "When was a door opened unto me in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:12",
        "answer": "when I came to Troas (to preach Christ's gospel)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:12, of whom was a door opened unto me?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:12",
        "answer": "of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 2:12.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 2:12",
        "answer": "Furthermore, when I came to Troas to preach Christ's gospel, and a door was opened unto me of the Lord,"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was opened unto me in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:12",
        "answer": "a door"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who in 2 Corinthians 2 is my brother?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:13",
        "answer": "Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:13, why did I have no rest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:13",
        "answer": "because I found not Titus my brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"I had no rest in my spirit, because I found not Titus.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 2:13",
        "answer": "my brother: but taking my leave of them, I went from thence into Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "From thence where did I go in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:13",
        "answer": "into Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who always causeth us to triumph in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:14",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:14, what does God make manifest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:14",
        "answer": "the savour of his knowledge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:14, where does God make manifest the savour of his knowledge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:14",
        "answer": "in every place"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 2 which uses the word: triumph",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 2:14",
        "answer": "Now thanks be unto God, which always causeth us to triumph in Christ, and maketh manifest the savour of his knowledge by us in every place."
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For we are unto God a sweet savour of Christ, in them that are saved, and in them that perish:",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 2:15",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 2:15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is sweet in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:15",
        "answer": "(we are) a sweet savour of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:15, in whom are we a sweet savour of Christ?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:15",
        "answer": "in them that are saved, and in them that perish"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For we are unto God a sweet savour of Christ, in them that are saved,and in them that perish:",
        "type": "",
        "reference": "2C 2:15",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 2:15"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 2:16.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 2:16",
        "answer": "To the one we are the savour of death unto death; and to the other the savour of life unto life. And who is sufficient for these things?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:16, unto what are we the savour of death?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:16",
        "answer": "death"
    },
    {
        "question": "Unto what are we the savour of life in 2 Corinthians 2 to the other?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:16",
        "answer": "life"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do many corrupt in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:17",
        "answer": "the word of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:17, in whose sight speak we in Christ?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:17",
        "answer": "in the sight of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For we are not as many, which corrupt the word of God.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 2:17",
        "answer": "but as of sincerity, but as of God, in the sight of God speak we in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:2, what do I make you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:2",
        "answer": "sorry"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And I wrote this same unto you, lest, when I came, I should have sorrow.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 2:3",
        "answer": "from them of whom I ought to rejoice; having confidence in you all, that my joy is the joy of you all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:3, what is the joy of you all?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:3",
        "answer": "my joy"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:3, what should I have from them of whom I ought to rejoice?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:3",
        "answer": "sorrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 2 which uses the word: tears",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "For out of much affliction and anguish of heart I wrote unto you with many tears; not that ye should be grieved, but that ye might know the love which I have more abundantly unto you."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:4, with what did I write unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "with many tears"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:4, why did I write unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "that ye might know the love which I have more abundantly unto you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:4, out of what did I write unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "out of much affliction and anguish of heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:4, how do I have love unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:4",
        "answer": "more abundantly"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:5, what may I not do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:5",
        "answer": "overcharge you all"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 2 have any caused?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:5",
        "answer": "grief"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was inflicted of many in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:6",
        "answer": "this punishment"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:6, to whom is this punishment sufficient?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:6",
        "answer": "to such a man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:7, what two things ought ye to do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:7",
        "answer": "rather to forgive him, and comfort him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:7, how might such a one be swallowed up?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:7",
        "answer": "with overmuch sorrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:8, what do I beseech you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:8",
        "answer": "that ye would confirm your love toward him"
    },
    {
        "question": "What confirm toward him in 2 Corinthians 2?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 2:8",
        "answer": "your love"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:9, why did I write?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:9",
        "answer": "(For to this end) that I might know the proof of you, (whether ye be obedient in all things)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 2:9, what might I know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 2:9",
        "answer": "the proof of you, (whether ye be obedient in all things)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 3 which uses the word: epistles",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 3:1",
        "answer": "Do we begin again to commend ourselves? or need we, as some others, epistles of commendation to you, or letters of commendation from you?"
    },
    {
        "question": "Do we begin to what in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:1",
        "answer": "(again to) commend ourselves"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:1, need we what two things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:1",
        "answer": "epistles of commendation to you, or letters of commendation from you"
    },
    {
        "question": "What excelleth in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:10",
        "answer": "the glory"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:10, what had no glory in this respect?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:10",
        "answer": "even that which was made glorious"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:11, what was glorious?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:11",
        "answer": "that which is done away"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:11, what is that which remaineth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:11",
        "answer": "(much more) glorious"
    },
    {
        "question": "What plainness do we use in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:12",
        "answer": "(great) plainness of speech"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:12, what do we have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:12",
        "answer": "(such) hope"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:13, where did Moses put a veil?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:13",
        "answer": "over his face"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who could not stedfastly look to the end of that which is abolished in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:13",
        "answer": "the children of Israel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who put a veil over his face in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:13",
        "answer": "Moses"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which reading is the veil not taken away in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:14",
        "answer": "in the reading of the old testament"
    },
    {
        "question": "What were blinded in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:14",
        "answer": "their minds (the minds of the children of Israel)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What remaineth untaken away until this day in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:14",
        "answer": "the same veil"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:14, where is the veil done away?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:14",
        "answer": "in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 3 which uses the word: reading",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 3:14",
        "answer": "But their minds were blinded: for until this day remaineth the same veil untaken away in the reading of the old testament; which veil is done away in Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:15, even unto what is the veil upon their heart?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:15",
        "answer": "this day"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:15, when is the veil upon their heart?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:15",
        "answer": "(even unto this day) when Moses is read"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:15, where is the veil?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:15",
        "answer": "upon their heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: But even unto this day, when Moses is read, the veil is upon their heart.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 3:15",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 3:15"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:16, when shall the veil be taken away?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:16",
        "answer": "when it shall turn to the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Nevertheless when it shall turn.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 3:16",
        "answer": "to the Lord, the veil shall be taken away"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where shall it turn in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:16",
        "answer": "to the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:16, what shall be taken away?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:16",
        "answer": "the veil"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:17, who is that Spirit?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:17",
        "answer": "the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 3:17.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 3:17",
        "answer": "Now the Lord is that Spirit: and where the Spirit of the Lord is, there is liberty."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is liberty in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:17",
        "answer": "where the Spirit of the Lord is"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 3 which uses the word: beholding",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 3:18",
        "answer": "But we all, with open face beholding as in a glass the glory of the Lord, are changed into the same image from glory to glory, even as by the Spirit of the Lord."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:18, with what are we beholding the glory of the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:18",
        "answer": "with open face"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are we beholding in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:18",
        "answer": "(as in a glass) the glory of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:18, how are we changed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:18",
        "answer": "into the same image from glory to glory, (even as by the Spirit of the Lord)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:2, what are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:2",
        "answer": "our epistle written in our hearts, known and read of all men"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Ye are our epistle written in our hearts, known and read of all men:",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 3:2",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 3:2"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where in 2 Corinthians 3 is our epistle written?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:2",
        "answer": "in our hearts"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was not written with ink in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:3",
        "answer": "the epistle of Christ (ministered by us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:3, of what are the fleshly tables?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:3",
        "answer": "of the heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are ye manifestly declared to be in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:3",
        "answer": "the epistle of Christ (ministered by us)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Forasmuch as ye are manifestly declared to be the epistle of Christ ministered by us, written.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 3:3",
        "answer": "not with ink, but with the Spirit of the living God; not in tables of stone, but in fleshly tables of the heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:3, with which spirit is the epistle of Christ written?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:3",
        "answer": "with the Spirit of the living God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:4, through whom have we such trust?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:4",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 3:5.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 3:5",
        "answer": "Not that we are sufficient of ourselves to think any thing as of ourselves; but our sufficiency is of God;"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is our sufficiency in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:5",
        "answer": "of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:6, of what hath God made us ministers?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:6",
        "answer": "of the new testament; (of the spirit)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:6, what giveth life?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:6",
        "answer": "the spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "What killeth in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:6",
        "answer": "the letter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was the ministration of death engraven and written in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:7",
        "answer": "in stones"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was engraven in stones in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:7",
        "answer": "the ministration of death"
    },
    {
        "question": "What could the children of Israel not stedfastly behold in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:7",
        "answer": "the face of Moses"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:8, what shall be rather glorious?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:8",
        "answer": "the ministration of the spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "What doth exceed in glory in 2 Corinthians 3?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 3:9",
        "answer": "the ministration of righteousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 3:9, what be glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 3:9",
        "answer": "the ministration of condemnation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:1, what have we received?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:1",
        "answer": "mercy"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:1, what do we not do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:1",
        "answer": "faint"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:10, what might be made manifest in our body?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:10",
        "answer": "the life also of Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are we bearing about in the body in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:10",
        "answer": "the dying of the Lord Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:11, where might the life also of Jesus be made manifest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:11",
        "answer": "in our mortal flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:11, where are we delivered?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:11",
        "answer": "unto death (for Jesus' sake)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:12, what worketh in us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:12",
        "answer": "death"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:12, what worketh in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:12",
        "answer": "life"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:13, of what do we have the same spirit?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:13",
        "answer": "faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:14, what two things shall he which raised up the Lord Jesus do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:14",
        "answer": "shall raise up us also by Jesus, and shall present us with you"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Knowing that he which raised up the Lord Jesus shall raise up.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 4:14",
        "answer": "us also by Jesus, and shall present us with you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:14, who shall raise us up?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:14",
        "answer": "he which raised up the Lord Jesus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 4 was abundant?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:15",
        "answer": "grace"
    },
    {
        "question": "What might redound to the glory of God in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:15",
        "answer": "the abundant grace (through the thanksgiving of many)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:15, what are for your sakes?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:15",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:16, who perishes?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:16",
        "answer": "our outward man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 4 which uses the word: renewed",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 4:16",
        "answer": "For which cause we faint not; but though our outward man perish, yet the inward man is renewed day by day."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is renewed day by day in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:16",
        "answer": "the inward man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:16, when is the inward man renewed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:16",
        "answer": "day by day"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For our light affliction, which is but for a moment, worketh for us a far more exceeding and eternal weight of glory;",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 4:17",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 4:17"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:17, what worketh for us a far more exceeding and eternal weight of glory?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:17",
        "answer": "our light affliction (which is but for a moment)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:17, what is but for a moment?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:17",
        "answer": "our light affliction"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 4:18.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 4:18",
        "answer": "While we look not at the things which are seen, but at the things which are not seen: for the things which are seen are temporal; but the things which are not seen are eternal."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:18, what are eternal?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:18",
        "answer": "the things which are not seen"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are temporal in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:18",
        "answer": "the things which are seen"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:18, at what do we look?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:18",
        "answer": "the things which are not seen"
    },
    {
        "question": "To what are we commending ourselves in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:2",
        "answer": "every man's conscience"
    },
    {
        "question": "How are we not walking in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:2",
        "answer": "in craftiness"
    },
    {
        "question": "What have we renounced in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:2",
        "answer": "the hidden things of dishonesty"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:2, by what are we commending ourselves to every man's conscience?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:2",
        "answer": "manifestation of the truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are we not handling deceitfully in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:2",
        "answer": "the word of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:3, to whom is our gospel hid?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:3",
        "answer": "to them that are lost"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 4:3.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 4:3",
        "answer": "But if our gospel be hid, it is hid to them that are lost:"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:3, if what be hid, it is hid to them that are lost?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:3",
        "answer": "our gospel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hath blinded the minds of them which believe not in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:4",
        "answer": "the god of this world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:4, why hath the god of this world blinded the minds of them which believe not?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:4",
        "answer": "lest the light of the glorious gospel of Christ (who is the image of God) should shine unto them"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the image of God in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:4",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"In whom the god of this world hath blinded the minds of them which believe.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 4:4",
        "answer": "not, lest the light of the glorious gospel of Christ, who is the image of God, should shine unto them"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:5, for whose sake do we preach ourselves your servants?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:5",
        "answer": "for Jesus' sake"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For we preach not ourselves, but Christ Jesus the Lord; and ourselves your servants for Jesus' sake.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 4:5",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 4:5"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:5, what two do we preach?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:5",
        "answer": "Christ Jesus the Lord; and ourselves your servants (for Jesus' sake)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:6, what did God command?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:6",
        "answer": "the light (to shine out of darkness)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who hath shined in out hearts in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:6",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:6, in what did God give the light of the knowledge of the glory of God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:6",
        "answer": "in the face of Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 4 which uses the word: shined",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 4:6",
        "answer": "For God, who commanded the light to shine out of darkness, hath shined in our hearts, to give the light of the knowledge of the glory of God in the face of Jesus Christ."
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 4:7.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 4:7",
        "answer": "But we have this treasure in earthen vessels, that the excellency of the power may be of God, and not of us."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do we have this treasure in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:7",
        "answer": "in earthen vessels"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:7, why do we have this treasure in earthen vessels?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:7",
        "answer": "that the excellency of the power may be of God, and not of us"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are we troubled in 2 Corinthians 4?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 4:8",
        "answer": "on every side"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:8, what two things are we?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:8",
        "answer": "troubled on every side, we are perplexed"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 4:9, not what two things are we?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 4:9",
        "answer": "not forsaken, not destroyed"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:1, how is the building of God not made?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:1",
        "answer": "with hands"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For we know that if our earthly house of this tabernacle were dissolved.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 5:1",
        "answer": "we have a building of God, an house not made with hands, eternal in the heavens"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is eternal in the heavens in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:1",
        "answer": "(we have) a building of God (an house not made with hands)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:1, if what were dissolved?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:1",
        "answer": "our earthly house of this tabernacle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 5 which uses the word: bad",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 5:10",
        "answer": "For we must all appear before the judgment seat of Christ; that every one may receive the things done in his body, according to that he hath done, whether it be good or bad."
    },
    {
        "question": "Before which seat must we appear in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:10",
        "answer": "the judgment seat of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:10, what may everyone receive?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:10",
        "answer": "the things done in his body (according to that he hath done, whether it be good or bad)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom do we persuade in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:11",
        "answer": "men"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Knowing therefore the terror of the Lord, we persuade men.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 5:11",
        "answer": "but we are made manifest unto God; and I trust also are made manifest in your consciences"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:11, in what two ways are we made manifest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:11",
        "answer": "unto God; and I trust also are made manifest in your consciences"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:11, what are we knowing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:11",
        "answer": "the terror of the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom may ye have somewhat to answer in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:12",
        "answer": "them which glory in appearance (and not in heart)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:12, what do we give you occasion to do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:12",
        "answer": "to glory on our behalf"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:13, what is to God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:13",
        "answer": "(it) whether we be beside ourselves"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:13, what is for your cause?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:13",
        "answer": "(it) whether we be sober"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:14, what do we thus judge?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:14",
        "answer": "that if one died for all, then were all dead"
    },
    {
        "question": "What constraineth us in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:14",
        "answer": "the love of Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For the love of Christ constraineth us; because we thus judge, that if one died for all, then were all dead:",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 5:14",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 5:14"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:14, who were dead?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:14",
        "answer": "all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:15, for whom did he die?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:15",
        "answer": "all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:15, how should they live?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:15",
        "answer": "(not live unto themselves, but) unto him which died for them, and rose again"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:16, how know we no man henceforth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:16",
        "answer": "after the flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:16, whom have we known after the flesh?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:16",
        "answer": "Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 5 which uses the word: creature",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 5:17",
        "answer": "Therefore if any man be in Christ, he is a new creature: old things are passed away; behold, all things are become new."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is a new creature in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:17",
        "answer": "(he) if any man be in Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What are passed away in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:17",
        "answer": "old things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:17, what are become new?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:17",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:18, what hath God given to us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:18",
        "answer": "the ministry of reconciliation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:18, how hath God reconciled us to himself?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:18",
        "answer": "by Jesus Christ"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was God reconciling unto himself in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:19",
        "answer": "the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:19, what did God not impute unto them?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:19",
        "answer": "their trespasses"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:19, what hath God committed unto us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:19",
        "answer": "the word of reconciliation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:2, what is from heaven?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:2",
        "answer": "our house"
    },
    {
        "question": "How are we desiring to be clothed upon with our house which is from heaven in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:2",
        "answer": "earnestly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose ambassadors are we in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:20",
        "answer": "Christ's"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 5:20.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 5:20",
        "answer": "Now then we are ambassadors for Christ, as though God did beseech you by us: we pray you in Christ's stead, be ye reconciled to God."
    },
    {
        "question": "In Christ's stead, what do we pray you in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:20",
        "answer": "be ye reconciled to God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:21, why hath God made him to be sin for us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:21",
        "answer": "that we might be made the righteousness of God in him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:21, what hath God made him to be for us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:21",
        "answer": "sin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"For he hath made him to be sin for us, who knew.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 5:21",
        "answer": "no sin; that we might be made the righteousness of God in him"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:3, how shall we not be found?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:3",
        "answer": "naked"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:4, who groan?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:4",
        "answer": "we that are in this tabernacle"
    },
    {
        "question": "What might mortality be in 2 Corinthians 5?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 5:4",
        "answer": "swallowed up of life."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:5, who hath wrought us for the selfsame thing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:5",
        "answer": "(he) God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:5, what hath God given us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:5",
        "answer": "the earnest of the Spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:6, when are we absent from the Lord?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:6",
        "answer": "whilst we are at home in the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:6, when are we confident?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:6",
        "answer": "always"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:7, by what do we walk?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:7",
        "answer": "by faith"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: (For we walk by faith, not by sight:)",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 5:7",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 5:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 5:8.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 5:8",
        "answer": "We are confident, I say, and willing rather to be absent from the body, and to be present with the Lord."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:8, from what are we willing to be absent?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:8",
        "answer": "the body"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:8, with whom are we willing to be present?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:8",
        "answer": "with the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:9, what may we be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:9",
        "answer": "accepted of him (the Lord)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 5:9, how may we be accepted of him?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 5:9",
        "answer": "whether present or absent"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:1, what receive you not in vain?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:1",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:1, as what together with him do we beseech you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:1",
        "answer": "workers"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: We then, as workers together with him, beseech you also that ye receive not the grace of God in vain.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 6:1",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 6:1"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:10, what are we possessing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:10",
        "answer": "all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:10, when are we rejoicing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:10",
        "answer": "alway"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:10, what are we making many?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:10",
        "answer": "rich"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 6 is open unto you?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:11",
        "answer": "our mouth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:11, what is enlarged?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:11",
        "answer": "our heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are ye straitened in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:12",
        "answer": "in your own bowels"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:13, what be ye also?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:13",
        "answer": "enlarged"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:13, how do I speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:13",
        "answer": "as unto my children"
    },
    {
        "question": "How be not unequally yoked in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:14",
        "answer": "(together) with unbelievers"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:14, which two's communion is questioned?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:14",
        "answer": "light (with) darkness"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 6 which uses the word: unrighteousness",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 6:14",
        "answer": "Be ye not unequally yoked together with unbelievers: for what fellowship hath righteousness with unrighteousness? and what communion hath light with darkness?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:14, which two's fellowship is questioned?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:14",
        "answer": "righteousness (with) unrighteousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:15, which two's concord is questioned?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:15",
        "answer": "Christ (with) Belial"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 6:15.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 6:15",
        "answer": "And what concord hath Christ with Belial? or what part hath he that believeth with an infidel?"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:15, who hath no part with an infidel?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:15",
        "answer": "he that believeth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:16, what shall they be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "my (God's) people"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And what agreement hath the temple of God with idols? for ye are the temple of the living God.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "as God hath said, I will dwell in them, and walk in them; and I will be their God, and they shall be my people"
    },
    {
        "question": "What hath no agreement with idols in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "the temple of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:16, who will dwell in them?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "(I) God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:16, who will walk in them?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "(I) God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:16, what are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:16",
        "answer": "the temple of the living God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:17, what be ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "separate"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:17, where come?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "out from among them"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:17, what will the Lord do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "I will receive you"
    },
    {
        "question": "What touch not in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "the unclean thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Wherefore come out from among them, and be ye separate, saith the Lord, and touch not the unclean thing; and I will receive you,",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 6:17",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 6:17"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:18, what will the Lord be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:18",
        "answer": "a Father unto you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:18, what shall ye be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:18",
        "answer": "my (the Lord's) sons and daughters"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Almighty in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:18",
        "answer": "the Lord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:2, when have I heard thee?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:2",
        "answer": "in a time accepted"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:2, when is the accepted time?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:2",
        "answer": "now"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 6:2.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 6:2",
        "answer": "(For he saith, I have heard thee in a time accepted, and in the day of salvation have I succoured thee: behold, now is the accepted time; behold, now is the day of salvation.)"
    },
    {
        "question": "When have I succoured thee in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:2",
        "answer": "in the day of salvation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 6 which uses the word: blamed",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 6:3",
        "answer": "Giving no offence in any thing, that the ministry be not blamed:"
    },
    {
        "question": "What be not blamed in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:3",
        "answer": "the ministry"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:3, where give no offence?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:3",
        "answer": "in any thing"
    },
    {
        "question": "As what approving ourselves in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:4",
        "answer": "the ministers of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But in all things approving ourselves as the ministers of God, in much patience.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 6:4",
        "answer": "in afflictions, in necessities, in distresses"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is unfeigned in 2 Corinthians 6?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 6:6",
        "answer": "love"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:7, of whom is the power?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:7",
        "answer": "of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:7, where is the armour of righteousness?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:7",
        "answer": "on the right hand and on the left"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: By the word of truth, by the power of God, by the armour of righteousness on the right hand and on the left,",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 6:7",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 6:7"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:7, what is on the right hand and on the left?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:7",
        "answer": "the armour of righteousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 6:8, what are two reports?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 6:8",
        "answer": "evil report and good report"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 7 which uses the word: filthiness",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 7:1",
        "answer": "Having therefore these promises, dearly beloved, let us cleanse ourselves from all filthiness of the flesh and spirit, perfecting holiness in the fear of God."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:1, what have we?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:1",
        "answer": "these promises"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what are we perfecting holiness in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:1",
        "answer": "in the fear of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "From what let us cleanse ourselves in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:1",
        "answer": "all filthiness of the flesh and spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:10, what worketh death?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:10",
        "answer": "the sorrow of the world"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 7:10.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 7:10",
        "answer": "For godly sorrow worketh repentance to salvation not to be repented of: but the sorrow of the world worketh death."
    },
    {
        "question": "What worketh repentance in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:10",
        "answer": "godly sorrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:11, what seven things were wrought in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:11",
        "answer": "what carefulness, clearing (of yourselves), indignation, fear, vehement desire, zeal, revenge"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:11, how did ye sorrow?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:11",
        "answer": "after a godly sort"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what are ye clear in this matter in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:11",
        "answer": "In all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is vehement in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:11",
        "answer": "vehement desire"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:12, what might appear unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:12",
        "answer": "our care for you (in the sight of God)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:12, why did I write unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:12",
        "answer": "that our care for you in the sight of God might appear unto you"
    },
    {
        "question": "In 2 Corinthians 7, whose spirit was refreshed by you all?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:13",
        "answer": "Titus' (his) spirit"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:13, for what did we joy exceedingly the more?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:13",
        "answer": "the joy of Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Therefore we were comforted in your comfort: yea, and exceedingly the more.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 7:13",
        "answer": "joyed we for the joy of Titus, because his spirit was refreshed by you all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:14, how did we speak all things to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:14",
        "answer": "in truth"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:14, where was our boasting made?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:14",
        "answer": "before Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:14, what is found a truth?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:14",
        "answer": "our boasting (which I made before Titus)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For if I have boasted any thing to him of you, I am not ashamed; but as we spake all things to you in truth, even so our boasting, which I made before Titus, is found a truth.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 7:14",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 7:14"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 7 did he remember?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:15",
        "answer": "the obedience of you all"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:15, what is more abundant toward you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:15",
        "answer": "his inward affection"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 7 which uses the word: affection",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 7:15",
        "answer": "And his inward affection is more abundant toward you, whilst he remembereth the obedience of you all, how with fear and trembling ye received him."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:15, with what two did ye receive him?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:15",
        "answer": "with fear and trembling"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:16, what do I have in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:16",
        "answer": "confidence"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:16, how do I have confidence in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:16",
        "answer": "in all things"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:2, what three have we done to no man?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:2",
        "answer": "we have wronged no man, we have corrupted no man, we have defrauded no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whom have we wronged in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:2",
        "answer": "no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:3, what have I said before?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:3",
        "answer": "that ye are in our hearts to die and live with you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:3, where are ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:3",
        "answer": "in our hearts"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:3, how do I speak this?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:3",
        "answer": "not to condemn you"
    },
    {
        "question": "How joyful am I in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:4",
        "answer": "exceeding joyful (in all our tribulation)"
    },
    {
        "question": "With what am I filled in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:4",
        "answer": "comfort"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:4, what two are great?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:4",
        "answer": "my boldness of speech (toward you) and my glorying of you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:5, where were we troubled?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:5",
        "answer": "on every side"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 7:5.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 7:5",
        "answer": "For, when we were come into Macedonia, our flesh had no rest, but we were troubled on every side; without were fightings, within were fears."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:5, what had no rest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:5",
        "answer": "our flesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:5, when did our flesh have no rest?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:5",
        "answer": "when we were come into Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:6, whom does God comfort?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:6",
        "answer": "those that are cast down"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Nevertheless God, that comforteth those that are cast down.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 7:6",
        "answer": "comforted us by the coming of Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:6, how did God comfort us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:6",
        "answer": "by the coming of Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was fervent in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:7",
        "answer": "your fervent mind (toward me)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:7, what three things did he tell us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:7",
        "answer": "your earnest desire, your mourning, your fervent mind toward me"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:7, by what was he comforted in you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:7",
        "answer": "by the consolation"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:8, how long did the same epistle make you sorry?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:8",
        "answer": "for a season"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:8, how did I make you sorry?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:8",
        "answer": "with a letter"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For though I made you sorry with a letter, I do not repent, though I did repent: for I perceive that the same epistle hath made you sorry, though it were but for a season.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 7:8",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 7:8"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:9, how were ye made sorry?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:9",
        "answer": "after a godly manner"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 7 which uses the word: damage",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 7:9",
        "answer": "Now I rejoice, not that ye were made sorry, but that ye sorrowed to repentance: for ye were made sorry after a godly manner, that ye might receive damage by us in nothing."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 7:9, why do I rejoice?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 7:9",
        "answer": "that ye sorrowed to repentance"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what might ye receive damage by us in 2 Corinthians 7?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 7:9",
        "answer": "nothing"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:1, what was bestowed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:1",
        "answer": "the grace of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:1, where was the grace of God bestowed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:1",
        "answer": "on the churches of Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Moreover, brethren, we do you to wit of the grace of God bestowed on the churches of Macedonia;",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 8:1",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 8:1"
    },
    {
        "question": "When be forward in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:10",
        "answer": "a year ago"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:10, what do I give?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:10",
        "answer": "my advice"
    },
    {
        "question": "What perform in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:11",
        "answer": "the doing of it"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:11, what may there be also out of that which ye have?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:11",
        "answer": "a performance"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:12, what is first?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:12",
        "answer": "a willing mind"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:12, how is it accepted?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:12",
        "answer": "according to that a man hath (and not according to that he hath not)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do I mean not in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:13",
        "answer": "not that other men be eased, and ye burdened"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:14, what may your abundance be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:14",
        "answer": "a supply for their want"
    },
    {
        "question": "What also may be a supply for your want in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:14",
        "answer": "their abundance"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:14, when may your abundance be a supply for their want?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:14",
        "answer": "now OR at this time"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 8 which uses the word: lack",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 8:15",
        "answer": "As it is written, He that had gathered much had nothing over; and he that had gathered little had no lack."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who had no lack in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:15",
        "answer": "he that had gathered little"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:15, who had nothing over?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:15",
        "answer": "He that had gathered much"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:16, what be to God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:16",
        "answer": "thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:16, where did God put the same earnest care for you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:16",
        "answer": "into the heart of Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 8:16.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 8:16",
        "answer": "But thanks be to God, which put the same earnest care into the heart of Titus for you."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:17, of what did Titus go unto you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:17",
        "answer": "of his own accord"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:17, what did Titus accept?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:17",
        "answer": "the exhortation"
    },
    {
        "question": "Throughout what is his praise in the gospel in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:18",
        "answer": "throughout all the churches"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:18, where is his praise?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:18",
        "answer": "in the gospel (throughout all the churches)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:19, of whom was he chosen to travel with us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:19",
        "answer": "of the churches"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:19, of what is the declaration?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:19",
        "answer": "of your ready mind"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what trial did the abundance of their joy abound in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:2",
        "answer": "in a great trial of affliction"
    },
    {
        "question": "What abounded unto the riches of their liberality in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:2",
        "answer": "the abundance of their joy and their (the Macedonian churches') deep poverty"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"How that in a great trial of affliction the abundance of their joy.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 8:2",
        "answer": "and their deep poverty abounded unto the riches of their liberality"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:2, of what were the riches?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:2",
        "answer": "of their liberality"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who should blame us in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:20",
        "answer": "no man"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:20, what is administered?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:20",
        "answer": "this abundance"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 8:21.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 8:21",
        "answer": "Providing for honest things, not only in the sight of the Lord, but also in the sight of men."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:21, in whose sight provide for honest things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:21",
        "answer": "not only in the sight of the Lord, but also in the sight of men"
    },
    {
        "question": "Providing for what in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:21",
        "answer": "for honest things (not only in the sight of the Lord, but also in the sight of men)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:22, whom have we proved diligent in many things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:22",
        "answer": "our brother"
    },
    {
        "question": "When have we proved our brother diligent in many things in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:22",
        "answer": "oftentimes"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is my fellowhelper in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:23",
        "answer": "Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are the messengers of the churches in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:23",
        "answer": "(Titus and) our brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is my partner in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:23",
        "answer": "Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:24, what show ye to them and before the churches?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:24",
        "answer": "the proof of your love, and of our boasting on your behalf"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:24, before whom show the proof of your love?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:24",
        "answer": "the churches"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 8:3.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 8:3",
        "answer": "For to their power, I bear record, yea, and beyond their power they were willing of themselves;"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:3, beyond what were they willing?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:3",
        "answer": "beyond their power"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 8 which uses the word: entreaty",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 8:4",
        "answer": "Praying us with much entreaty that we would receive the gift, and take upon us the fellowship of the ministering to the saints."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:4, what two things did they pray us that we would do?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:4",
        "answer": "that we would receive the gift, and take upon us the fellowship of the ministering to the saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:4, with what did they pray us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:4",
        "answer": "with much entreaty"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:5, when did they give their own selves to the Lord and unto us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:5",
        "answer": "first"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"And this they did, not as we hoped, but first gave their own selves.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 8:5",
        "answer": "to the Lord, and unto us by the will of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:5, by what did they give their own selves to the Lord and unto us?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:5",
        "answer": "by the will of God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What would Titus finish in you in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:6",
        "answer": "the same grace (also)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:6, whom did we desire so he would finish in you the same grace also?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:6",
        "answer": "Titus"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:7, in what six do ye abound?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:7",
        "answer": "in every thing, in faith, and utterance, and knowledge, and in all diligence, and in your love to us"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:8, by what occasion do I speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:8",
        "answer": "by occasion of the forwardness of others"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:8, not by what do I speak?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:8",
        "answer": "not by commandment"
    },
    {
        "question": "To prove what, do I speak in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:8",
        "answer": "the sincerity of your love"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: For ye know the grace of our Lord Jesus Christ, that, though he was rich, yet for your sakes he became poor, that ye through his poverty might be rich.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 8:9",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 8:9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Through his poverty, what might ye be in 2 Corinthians 8?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 8:9",
        "answer": "rich"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 8:9, what know ye?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 8:9",
        "answer": "the grace of our Lord Jesus Christ (that, though he was rich, yet for your sakes he became poor, that ye through his poverty might be rich)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is superfluous in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:1",
        "answer": "(For as touching the ministering to the saints) (it) for me to write to you"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:1, as touching what, is it superfluous for me to write to you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:1",
        "answer": "the ministering to the saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:1, what is it for me to write to you as touching the ministering to the saints?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:1",
        "answer": "superfluous"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who minister bread for your food in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:10",
        "answer": "he that ministereth seed to the sower"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 9 which uses the word: sower",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 9:10",
        "answer": "Now he that ministereth seed to the sower both minister bread for your food, and multiply your seed sown, and increase the fruits of your righteousness;)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What multiply in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:10",
        "answer": "your seed sown"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:10, what increase?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:10",
        "answer": "the fruits of your righteousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Being enriched in every thing to all bountifulness, which causeth through us thanksgiving to God.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 9:11",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 9:11"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does all bountifulness cause in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:11",
        "answer": "(through us) thanksgiving to God"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what are ye being enriched in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:11",
        "answer": "in every thing (to all bountifulness)"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the administration of this service supply in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:12",
        "answer": "the want of the saints"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:12, by what is the administration of this service abundant?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:12",
        "answer": "by many thanksgivings unto God"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:13, for what two things do they glorify God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:13",
        "answer": "for your professed subjection unto the gospel of Christ, and for your liberal distribution (unto them, and unto all men)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:13, whom do they glorify?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:13",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is liberal in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:13",
        "answer": "your liberal distribution (unto them, and unto all men)"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"Whiles by the experiment of this ministration they glorify God.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 9:13",
        "answer": "for your professed subjection unto the gospel of Christ, and for your liberal distribution unto them, and unto all men"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:14, for what do they long after you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:14",
        "answer": "for the exceeding grace of God in you"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 9:14.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 9:14",
        "answer": "And by their prayer for you, which long after you for the exceeding grace of God in you."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:14, what is for you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:14",
        "answer": "their prayer"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:15, what be unto God?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:15",
        "answer": "Thanks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: Thanks be unto God for his unspeakable gift.",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 9:15",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 9:15"
    },
    {
        "question": "What in 2 Corinthians 9 is unspeakable?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:15",
        "answer": "his (God's) unspeakable gift"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:2, what do I know?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:2",
        "answer": "the forwardness of your mind"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was ready a year ago in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:2",
        "answer": "Achaia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:2, to whom do I boast of you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:2",
        "answer": "to them of Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What hath provoked many in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:2",
        "answer": "your zeal"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:3, what may ye be?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:3",
        "answer": "ready"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:3, what should be in vain?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:3",
        "answer": "our boasting of you (in this behalf)"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:3, whom have I sent?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:3",
        "answer": "the brethren"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:4, in what should we be ashamed?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:4",
        "answer": "in this same confident boasting"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:4, how might they of Macedonia find you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:4",
        "answer": "unprepared"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who might find you unprepared in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:4",
        "answer": "they of Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:5, not as of what might the same be ready?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:5",
        "answer": "covetousness"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:5, when would they make up your bounty?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:5",
        "answer": "before hand"
    },
    {
        "question": "What did I think it necessary to do in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:5",
        "answer": "to exhort the brethren (that they would go before unto you, and make up before hand your bounty)"
    },
    {
        "question": "How in 2 Corinthians 9 shall he which soweth bountifully reap?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:6",
        "answer": "bountifully"
    },
    {
        "question": "How shall he which soweth sparingly reap in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:6",
        "answer": "sparingly"
    },
    {
        "question": "Finish this verse: \"But this I say, He which soweth sparingly shall reap.\"",
        "type": "F",
        "reference": "2C 9:6",
        "answer": "also sparingly; and he which soweth bountifully shall reap also bountifully"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:6, who are the two sowers?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:6",
        "answer": "He which soweth sparingly and he which soweth bountifully"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who loveth a cheerful giver in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:7",
        "answer": "God"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote the verse from 2 Corinthians 9 which uses the word: cheerful",
        "type": "K",
        "reference": "2C 9:7",
        "answer": "Every man according as he purposeth in his heart, so let him give; not grudgingly, or of necessity: for God loveth a cheerful giver."
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:7, what two ways is a man not to give?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:7",
        "answer": "not grudgingly, or of necessity"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:7, how let every man give?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:7",
        "answer": "(according) as he purposeth in his heart"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:8, what do ye have in all things?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:8",
        "answer": "all sufficiency"
    },
    {
        "question": "Give the reference: And God is able to make all grace abound toward you; that ye, always having all sufficiency in all things, may abound to every good work:",
        "type": "G",
        "reference": "2C 9:8",
        "answer": "2 Corinthians 9:8"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:8, to what may ye abound?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:8",
        "answer": "to every good work"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:8, what is God able to make abound toward you?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:8",
        "answer": "all grace"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:9, when does his righteousness remain?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:9",
        "answer": "for ever"
    },
    {
        "question": "According to 2 Corinthians 9:9, to whom hath he given?",
        "type": "R",
        "reference": "2C 9:9",
        "answer": "to the poor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where hath he dispersed in 2 Corinthians 9?",
        "type": "P",
        "reference": "2C 9:9",
        "answer": "abroad"
    },
    {
        "question": "Quote this verse: 2 Corinthians 9:9.",
        "type": "Q",
        "reference": "2C 9:9",
        "answer": "(As it is written, He hath dispersed abroad; he hath given to the poor: his righteousness remaineth for ever."
    }
]